人人字幕组 ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
最新最快海外影视字幕下载请登陆 www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译｜Izecson　辣辣　盐湖凉开水　Eunice　Lynn_宁　戴普普　Alex
杏仁斯嘉丽　海边的微子酱　牛的牵牵　郝先生快好起来　咖喱味的虚寒
时间轴｜Ans　aaaBao　林卡　木瓜一号　噃噃bobo　孙了个大圣　壬虚浪影　Jimmy贝壳
校对｜小酸奶　　后期｜8T　　总监｜somehacker　小酸奶
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
海边的曼彻斯特
[克劳迪娅·玛丽号]
关于这个世界 他有好多都不理解
A lot of stuff that he just doesn't understand about the world
但我理解 所以这指引着我处世的
that I understand that makes ... it makes all my actions
所作所为
when I move through the world...
我做得更好
I do things better
因为在我看来它像地图一样清晰明确
because I can see it all laid out like a map.
你看过地图吗
Have you ever looked at a map?
- 看过 如果我没看错  - 你知道怎么看吗
- Yes. When I'm not mistaken.  - Do you know how to read a map?
- 你知道怎么看地图吗  - 知道
- Do you know how to read a map?  - Yeah.
你爸爸是个相当不错的人
Your father's a perfectly good guy,
但关于这个世界
but there's a lot of stuff
他有很多都看不透
that he just doesn't understand about the world
- 我却能  - 我爸爸
- that I understand.  - My dad...
- 停 听着  - 我爸爸
- Wait. Listen.  - My daddy's...
我还没问你问题呢
I haven't asked you a question yet.
I haven't asked you a question.
- 听着  - 我爸爸
- Listen. Shh.  - My daddy...
别告诉你妈妈 闭嘴 安静
Don't tell your mother. Shut up! By quiet.
安静 我还没问你问题呢
Shush. I haven't asked you the question yet.
我什么都没问你呢 听着
I haven't asked you anything. Listen. Shh.
安静 我们没事 别担心
Quiet. We got it. Don't worry about it.
听着
Listen.
如果
If there was...
如果你只能带一个人跟你去孤岛
if you could take one guy to an island with you
你知道跟他在一起你是安全的 因为他最厉害
and you knew you'd be safe because he was the best man
他会弄明白如何生存
and he was going to figure out how to survive,
他会做一切
he was going to make everything...
让你们在岛上幸福地生活
make the world a good place on the island,
他会一直让你开开心心的
he was going to keep you happy,
他是这项工作的最佳人选
he... this is the best man for the job, no matter what,
如果你必须在我和你爸爸之间选一个
if it was between me and your father,
- 你会选谁  - 我爸爸
- who would you say?  - My daddy.
我不明白 等一下
I don't see... hang on a second.
等一下 听着
Hang on a second. Listen.
我觉得你弄错了
I think you're wrong about that.
虽然确实是你来选 但我想让你明白
It's your choice to make, but I want you to understand something:
有很多
That there's a lot of...
选…怎么 你干什么
Pick up... what hap... what is that?
你不能把鱼竿丢下不管
You can't leave your fishing rod like that.
我不明白为什么它一直滴水
I don't know why the hell it keeps dripping.
一整晚 不停地滴 滴 滴
All night long... drip, drip, drip.
这破玩意我都让人修了十次了
I've had the fucking thing repaired ten times.
你需要一个新的塞子
You need a new stopper.
是吗
Is that it?
你的塞子
Your stopper's...
边缘都烂掉了
it's rotted all around the edges,
所以堵不住了
so it's not making a seal.
水就会从洗手池下面滴出去
The water's going to drip through to the bowl.
我可以
I could, uh...
我可以明天给你拿个新的
I could bring you a new one tomorrow.
或者你考虑一下把整个水池换掉
Or you might want to consider replacing the whole apparatus.
你建议我怎么做
What do you recommend?
我可以先换掉塞子
I could replace the stopper first.
如果这还不管用的话
If that doesn't work,
我就帮你换掉整个水池
I could replace the whole apparatus.
你没法给我专业意见吗
You can't give me a professional recommendation?
其实都取决于你
Well, it's really up to you.
明天我小姨子要带着侄子们过来
Tomorrow my sister-in-law's coming over with the nephews.
我得开车去接
I got to take the car in.
不 是我的妹妹简宁的大女儿的成年礼
No, it's my sister Jeanine's oldest daughter's bat mitzvah.
两百艘船沉没
Sank 200 ships...
我可能会无聊得要死
I'm looking forward to being bored to death.
风暴表明需要更多
The storm demonstrated the need for more...
那女孩不想办 他爸爸也不想
The girl doesn't want it, her father doesn't want it,
更别说我了
and don't even ask me.
要坐七个小时车
Seven hours in the car.
督促他们离开城市
...charge and leave their cities...
我真想割喉自杀
I could really slit my throat.
但那些小姑娘们很漂亮
But oh, well. The little girls are charming.
李 抱歉
Lee, I'm so sorry.
没事
That's okay.
太恶心了
This is so gross.
没关系
That's all right.
不 让他来吧
No, tell him to come.
好 好
Okay. Yeah.
但辛迪 我得告诉你件事
But... but... but, Cindy, I have to tell you something.
我爱上了我公寓的管理员
I'm, like, in love with my janitor.
是不是很变态
Is that sick?
你对勤杂工有过性幻想吗
Have you ever had a sexual fantasy about your handyman?
挺尴尬的 因为他其实是在
Well, it's awkward because he's literally, like,
疏通我马桶里的屎
cleaning the shit out of my toilet bowl right now,
而且我现在没那么性感
and I don't think I'm at my most alluring.
对 或许你说得对
Yeah, maybe you're right.
我又不是在社交场合见到他的
It's not like I met him socially.
好 谢谢 辛迪
Okay, thank you, Cindy.
好 二十分钟后见 再见
Okay. Like 20 minutes. Bye.
你好 都好了
Uh, hi. All set.
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
不客气
You're welcome.
我能给你点小费[提示]吗
Can I give you a tip?
你是说建议
You mean like a suggestion?
不 我想说小费
No. I mean like a tip.
好 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
- 好  - 好
- Okay.  - Okay.
晚安
Good night.
晚安 再见
Good night. Goodbye.
我还得修多少次这破水管
I mean, how many times do I have to fix these fucking pipes?
我每次洗澡
Every time I take a shower,
整个房子都淹了
the entire apartment has a flood.
我简直要疯了
It's driving me insane.
我明天给你带个水管工过来
Well, I'll get you a plumber here tomorrow,
但我们得把所有地砖都刨开
but I'd say we're going to have to break through the tile
确定渗漏点
and isolate the leak because
因为下面有好多水
there's quite a lot of water down there.
你怎么知道是因为我 为什么自然就想到是我
How do you know it's me? Why is it automatically me?
因为如果是楼上漏的
Because if it was coming from higher up,
你家的天花板上或者墙上
you'd have water damage in your ceiling
会有漏水的痕迹 但这些地方都是干的
or in your wall, and it's all dry.
好极了
Great.
可能只是嵌缝
It might just be the caulking.
整个浴缸都需要重新弥缝
This whole tub needs to be recaulked.
你最近几小时泡过澡或者冲过淋浴吗
Have you taken a bath or a shower in the last couple of hours?
洗过
Yes.
应该就是这个原因了
It might just be that.
好 你怎么查明是不是
Okay. And how are you planning to find that out?
我们可以打开淋浴喷头 看它是不是往楼下滴水
Well, we could run the shower and see if it drips downstairs.
你想让我现在洗淋浴
Oh, you want me to take a shower right now?
不
No.
你想让我现在洗澡
You want me to take a shower right now
好让你在旁边看着
while you stand there watching to see
水会不会渗到弗里德里希家
if it drips into the Friedrichs' apartment?
我才不在乎你干什么 奥尔森夫人
I don't give a fuck what you do, Mrs. Olsen.
我只是想修好漏水的地方
I'm just trying to fix the fucking leak.
我喜欢
I... I like that.
你真是大胆 竟然这么跟我说话
How dare you talk to me like that.
快给我滚出去
Get the fuck out of my fucking house.
- 好  - 快滚出去
- Okay.  - Get the fuck
不然我就报警了
out of my fucking house before I call the police.
好
All right.
你听见没 我说滚
Did you hear me? I said get out.
我做不到 你堵着门呢
I can't. You're blocking the doorway.
你到底什么毛病
What the fuck's the matter with you?
你不能那么跟房客说话
You can't talk to the tenants like that.
李 你活干得很好 人也可靠
Look, Lee, you do good work. You're dependable.
但总有人跟我投诉你
But I get these complaints all the time.
你粗鲁 不友好
You're rude, you're unfriendly.
连“早上好”的招呼都不打 拜托
You won't say good morning. I mean, come on.
埃默里先生 我修水管
Mr. Emery, I fix the plumbing,
带走垃圾 帮他们刷墙
take out the garbage, paint their apartments.
我做电工活 你我都明白这是违法的
I do electrical work, which we both know is against the law.
每天准时上班
I show up on time.
给四栋楼做维修
I'm working four buildings,
钱全被你拿走了
and you're getting all the money.
所以随便你怎么做吧
So do whatever you're going to do.
你愿意对奥尔森夫人道歉吗
Would you be willing to apologize to Mrs. Olsen?
为什么
For what?
好吧 好吧 我跟她谈
All right. All right. I'll talk to her.
- 给 李  - 谢了
- Here, Lee.  - Thanks.
- 你好吗  - 好
- How are you doing?  - Good.
近来如何
How's things going, all right?
还行吧
Yeah.
看比赛吗
Watch the game?
看了
Yeah, I did.
你觉得他们能赢吗
You think they got a shot?
- 不能  - 你确定
- No.  - You bet?
是啊
Yeah, I would.
他们前两局落后了 后三局也会输的
They dropped the first two. They're going to lose the next three.
- 给你  - 谢谢
- Here you go.  - Thanks.
天啊 太抱歉了
Oh, my god. I'm so sorry.
没事
That's okay.
我泼到你了吗
Did I get you?
嗯
Yes.
- 我泼到你了  - 没事的
- I got you.  - That's okay.
- 我给你拿几张纸巾  - 没事
- Let me get you some napkins.  - I'm okay.
兰妮 帮我拿几张纸巾
Hey, Lenny, can I grab some napkins?
谢了
Thanks.
谢谢
Thank you.
给
Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
没事
It's okay.
我把酒都泼到你身上了
Well, now I spilled my beer all over you,
- 我叫莎伦  - 谢谢
- my name's Sharon.  - Thank you.
没事的
Uh, it's okay.
你是
And you are?
李
Uh, Lee.
- 随便问个人  - 好
- Ask anybody.  - Okay.
他来了
Here he comes.
近况如何
How you doing?
- 你近况如何  - 好 我很好
- How you doing?  - Good. I'm good.
我能问你们一下 你们认识我吗
Hey, can I ask you guys, do you know me?
- 不认识  - 我也不认识
- Uh, I don't think so.  - Yeah, I don't think so either.
我们没见过吗
We never met?
- 没有  - 没有 没见过
- No.  - No, not yet.
- 没见过  - 没见过
- No, I don't think so.  - No.
所以你们他妈的为什么盯着我看
So what the fuck are you looking at me for?
- 什么  - 我说你们为什么盯着我看
- Excuse me?  - I said what the fuck are you looking at me for?
- 出去走走冷静一下  - 先生 我们没看你
- Hey, take a fuckin' walk.  - Sir, we weren't looking at you.
不 别对这混蛋道歉
No, don't apologize to this asshole.
- 滚开  - 讲真的 我们没在看你
- Take a fuckin' hike.  - We weren't looking at you, seriously.
住手 伙计
Come on, man! Hey!
放开我 我来让你滚蛋
Let me go! I gotta go take a hike!
我来让你滚蛋
I wanna take a fuckin' hike!
你好 我是李
Hello, this is Lee.
好的
Oh. Okay.
什么时候的事
When did that happen?
他现在怎么样了
Well, how's he doing now?
不 不用
No, don't do that.
我现在就过去
I'm gonna come up there right now.
一个半小时后到
I'll be up there in an hour and a half.
行吗
Okay?
谢谢
Thank you.
再见
Bye.
埃默里先生 我是李 我刚联系约瑟
Mr. Emery, it's Lee again. I contacted Jose.
他至少能替我到周五晚上
He can cover me till Friday night at least.
在那之后
Uh, after that,
吉尼·迈卡迪夫会一直替到我回来为止
Gene Macadavey will take over until I get back.
在你找到能干的管子工之前
I wouldn't do anything with the Mr. and Mrs. Friedrichs' ceiling
我建议你别去动天花板
until you you get a real plumber in there.
不过你估计也做不了什么
But what are you gonna do?
一有消息我就告诉你
I will, uh, let you know as soon as I have more information.
我可能会在曼彻斯特至少待一周
I should be in Manchester a week at least.
非常感谢 再见
Thank you very much. Bye.
快点啊
Come on!
快开
Go!
19号出口
松树街
曼彻斯特
距北贝弗利还有0.5英里
社工请到住院处
Social services volunteer to inpatient admitting.
我们能让一名社工到住院处去吗
Can we get a social services volunteer to inpatient admitting?
- 李  - 他死了吗
- Hey, Lee.  - Is he dead?
我很遗憾 李
I'm sorry, Lee.
他大约一小时前去世了
He passed away about an hour ago.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
- 你见到他了吗  - 没有
- Did you see him?  - No.
- 我带他来的  - 乔治带他来的
- I mean, I brought him in.  - George brought him in.
我们今早在看船
We were looking at the boat this morning,
然后他就
and he just...
我不知道 他就 摔倒了
I don't know, he just, like, fell over.
刚开始以为他在开玩笑
I thought he was kidding me at first.
接着我叫了救护车 然后…
Then I called the ambulance, and, uh...
就成这样了
That was it.
我去叫穆勒医生说你到了
I'll just call Dr. Muller and tell him that you're here.
贝瑟尼医生在哪
Where's Dr. Betheny?
她在休产假 他来了
Oh, she's on maternity leave. Here he is.
李 我是穆勒医生 我们之前通过话
Lee, I'm Dr. Muller. We spoke on the phone.
- 你好  - 我非常非常遗憾
- Yeah, hi.  - I'm very, very sorry.
- 谢谢  - 你好 乔治
- Thank you.  - Hello, George.
- 你好 吉姆  - 你还好吧
- Hiya, Jim.  - How you holding up?
很好 你知道
Oh, great, you know?
- 今天是悲伤的一天  - 对
- It's a very sad day.  - Yeah.
我哥在哪
Where's my brother?
他在楼下 你要想的话可以去见他
Oh, he's downstairs. You can see him if you want.
他怎么了
What happened to him?
心跳骤停
Just a cardiac arrest.
你知道他的心脏现在很弱
You know his heart's very weak at this point.
它就停跳了
It just gave out.
很遗憾你没能及时赶过来
I'm really sorry you couldn't get here in time,
但就像我之前所说…
but as I told you before...
别说了
Aw, fuck this.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 没事的 伙计  - 没事的
- That's okay, buddy.  - That's perfectly all right.
有人打电话给我舅吗
Did anybody call my uncle?
他们的唐尼舅舅
It's their uncle Donny.
对 我舅妈和我舅
Yeah, my aunt and uncle.
- 应该有人打…  - 不 李
- Somebody should have called...  - No, Lee. Lee, no.
- 怎么了  - 唐尼在明尼苏达找了工作
- What? What?  - Donny got a job in Minnesota.
- 大概就之前不久  - 明尼苏达
- Like, a while ago.  - Minnesota?
如果你相信的话
Yeah, he got a job in some outfit
他在明尼苏达明内通卡的
in Mnnetonka, Minnesota,
一家服装公司找了份工作
if you can believe that.
- 乔没跟你说吗  - 没有
- Joe didn't tell you about that?  - No.
海洛温医生 如果你在四层
Dr. Hallerin, if you're on fourth floor,
请到护士站来一下
please come to the nurses station.
如果你想的话我可以打电话给他 李
I can call him if you want, Lee,
告诉他发生了什么事
and tell him what happened.
- 好的 谢了  - 没事
- Okay, thanks.  - No problem.
告诉他发生了什么事
Tell him what happened.
告诉他我会今晚打电话给他
Tell him I'll call him tonight.
商议一下后事
Talk about arrangements.
还得有人打电话给我老婆
Somebody should call my wife.
- 你的…  - 前妻
- Your, uh, uh...  - Ex-wife.
- 你是说兰迪吗  - 兰迪
- You mean Randi?  - Randi.
- 对 抱歉 就是兰迪  - 没问题
- Yes, I'm sorry. I meant Randi.  - That's okay.
我之前就想到了 我会打电话给她的
I already thought of that. I'll take care of it.
- 好的 谢了  - 不客气
- Okay. Thank you.  - No problem.
- 我现在能看他了吗  - 当然
- Can I see him now?  - Sure.
李 我能在这等着
Lee, I can wait up here.
李 如果你有什么需要
Lee, if you need anything.
好的
Okay.
- 谢谢  - 不客气
- Thanks.  - Yeah.
你要纸巾吗
Would you like a Kleenex?
- 好 谢谢  - 不客气
- Yeah, thanks. Yeah.  - Yeah.
我能拿两张纸巾吗
Can I get a couple Kleenex, please?
谢了 亲爱的
Thanks, hon.
- 抱歉  - 没关系的
- I'm sorry.  - Oh, please.
- 贝瑟尼医生怎么样了  - 她很好
- How is Dr. Betheny?  - Oh, she's doing very well.
她刚生了一对双胞胎女儿
She just had twin girls.
- 艾琳和我说了  - 对
- Oh, Irene told me that.  - Yeah.
我下午给她打电话说了发生的事情
I call this afternoon and tell her what happened.
她对他很好
She was very good to him.
她确实
Yeah, she was.
这种病通常被称作充血性心力衰竭
The disease is commonly referred to as congestive heart failure.
- 我的天  - 你熟悉这种病吗
- Oh, my God.  - Are you familiar with it?
- 不  - 那你刚才为什么说“我的天”
- No.  - Then what are you saying "Oh, my God" for?
因为 到底是什么病
Because... what is it?
她正想解释 亲爱的
She's trying to explain it, honey.
- 抱歉 贝瑟…  - 贝瑟尼医生
- I'm sorry, Dr. Beth...  - Betheny.
- 贝瑟尼 抱歉  - 没关系
- Betheny, I'm sorry.  - Not a problem.
所以你接着说
So you were saying.
是一种心脏肌肉的逐渐衰竭
It's a gradual deterioration of the muscles of the heart.
通常发生在老年人身上
It's usually associated with older people.
但也有极个别病例发生在年轻人身上
But in rare cases, it will occur in a younger person.
一些人五六十年间
Some people live up to 50-60 years
只会偶然发病一次
with just an occasional attack.
但大多数患者发病有周期性
But most people suffer periodic episodes,
会像你在周一那样
like the one you had on Monday,
出现进一步削弱肌肉的
which mimic the symptoms of a heart attack,
类心脏病症状
and which further weaken the muscle.
可能会让你卧床一到两周
They can put you out of commission for a week, two weeks.
你需要住院好让我们实时监测心脏情况
And you'll need to be hospitalized so we can monitor your heart,
因为这一两周内心跳骤停的风险很大
because the risk of cardiac arrest is elevated for a week or two.
我的天
Oh, my God.
- 但一般情况下  - 没关系
- But in between,   - It's okay.
大多数患者感觉很健康
most people feel perfectly healthy.
可以过基本的正常生活
You can basically live a normal life.
等等 你说一些人活了五六十年是什么意思
Wait. So what do you mean some people live to be 50-60 years?
你是说只活到五六十岁
I mean, are you saying total?
还是说在他们被确诊后还活了五六十年
Or are saying when they're diagnosed with this?
还是怎样 到底是什么意思
Or what? What are you saying?
告诉我实情吧
And tell me the fuckin' truth.
只活到五六十岁
Total.
绝大多数像你这种情况的患者
For most people with the particulars of your condition,
平均还能再活五到十年
the average life expectancy is five to ten years.
统计数据差异很大
The statistics vary widely.
统计数字不能代表你
You're not a statistic.
你只是一个个体
You're just one person,
我们不知道你将来会怎样
and we don't know what's gonna happen to you yet.
但这不什么好病
But it's not a good disease.
什么是疾病
What is a good disease?
- 接触毒漆引起的皮疹  - 脚癣吗
- Poison Ivy.  - Athlete's foot?
- 简直在搞笑  - 伊莉斯 拜托
- It's a comedy routine.  - Elise, please.
- 看在上帝的份上  - 我的天
- For Christ's sake.  - Oh, my God!
你什么时候才能不挑我刺
When am I gonna put one foot right?
- 给点提示怎么样  - 伊莉斯…
- How about a hint?  - Elise...
- 爸  - 怎么了
- Daddy.  - What?
她没事
She's fine.
我们都很难过
We're all upset.
我们要继续听
We're all gonna listen,
然后问我们能想到的所有问题
then we're gonna ask any of the questions we wanna ask,
接着我们看能一起做点什么 对吗
and then we're gonna figure out what to do together, right?
- 对  - 当然
- Right.  - Sure.
那你接着说 贝瑟医生
So you were saying, Dr. Beth.
- 贝瑟尼 爸  - 贝瑟尼医生 爸
- Betheny, Dad.  - It's Dr. Betheny, Dad.
把名字说对了
Get it right.
我不知道你们现在哪里来的幽默感
I do not see where the humor lies in this situation.
- 伊莉斯 你要冷静  - 不
- Elise, you must calm down.  - No.
- 抱歉 我不想…  - 不 别
- I'm sorry, I'm not trying to...  - No, no, don't.
别说了 我待不下去了 不
No more. I'm not gonna. Nope.
- 伊莉斯 我给你拿杯水吧  - 不用
- Elise, let me get you a glass of water.  - No.
- 爸 算了吧  - 就像你一样算了吧
- Daddy, forget it.  - Forget it like you.
每个人都该像你
Everybody should be just like you.
你知道吗 我不想在这当坏人了
You know what? I am tired of being the bad guy here.
老天 现在躺在医院里的是谁
Jesus Christ! Who's in the fuckin' hospital here?
对对 所以我是坏蛋
Right. Right. So I'll be the bad guy,
你在医院向你儿子解释笑话去吧
and you be in the hospital and explain the jokes to your son.
- 我回家了  - 你要回家了
- I'm going home.  - You're going home?
- 你要回家了  - 对
- You're going home?  - Yep!
- 我去把她拉回来  - 去她的
- Let me get her back.  - Fuck her.
- 别再那样说了  - 闭嘴
- Come on with that stuff already!  - Stop that shit!
谢谢 托尼
Thank you, Tony.
谢谢
Thank you.
我得去趟曼彻斯特
I have to get up to Manchester.
没人告诉帕特里克 对吗
Nobody told Patrick, right?
没有 你让我们在这等你回来
No, you had asked for us to wait for you to get here.
- 对 谢了  - 不用谢
- Yes. Thank you.  - Okay.
那么
So, um,
接下来的流程是怎样的
what is the procedure now?
你得和殡仪馆协调安排
Oh, now you have to make arrangements with a funeral parlor.
他们会很好地照料后事
And they pretty much take care of everything.
我一个殡仪馆的名字都不知道
I don't know the name of one.
没关系 我们可以帮你
That's all right. We can help you with that.
对
Oh, yeah.
然后他们就会过来把他带走吗
And they'll just come and pick him up?
- 对  - 对
- Yeah.  - Yes.
- 我能去打电话 李  - 好的
- I can make those calls, Lee.  - Okay.
如果有需要帮忙的随时告诉我
Let me know if you need any help with anything.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
对了 我们还要谈谈
Yeah, we've gotta talk about the boat
船和网站的事
and the website,
还有其他的一切
and all that.
当然 我随时都在
Sure. I'm around.
我得在学校放学前赶过去 所以…
I gotta get up there before school let's out, so...
你只需要签字领走乔的遗物
You just have to sign for Joe's belongings.
这边走
Right this way.
在这里签字就行
Just gotta sign right here.
海洛温医生 如果你在四层
Dr. Hallerin, if you're on fourth floor,
请到护士站
please come to the nurses station.
乔的东西呢 就是放在这的那个塑料袋
Where's Joe's belongings? The plastic bag right here.
不好意思 稍等一下
Sorry. Give me a sec.
乔的东西呢
Where's Joe's belongings?
对 就这样 很好
All right, all right. That's good. Hup!
- 这样吗  - 对 但是拇指要远离鱼线
- Like that?  - Yeah, but keep your thumb off the line,
不然鱼上钩的时候一扯
because, if you get a strike,
鱼线就会把你的拇指划一个大口子
it's gonna slice it right open,
你知道之后会发生什么吗
and you know what happens then?
- 什么  - 鲨鱼闻到血的味道
- What?  - The sharks will smell the blood,
就会把咱们的船撕碎
and they'll rip this boat apart.
- 它们不会的  - 当然会
- No, they won't.  - Yeah, they will.
爸 是真的吗
Dad, will they?
- 是的  - 骗人
- Yes, sir.  - Shut up.
我见过一群鲨鱼把船撕成了碎片
You know, I seen a school of sharks tear a boat to pieces
就像那船是纸板做的似的
like it was made of cardboard,
就因为有个小孩往水里扔了个创可贴
because some kid threw a band-aid in the water.
是的
Oh, yeah.
是有这么件事
Yeah, he did.
- 就是这样  - 骗人
- Oh, yeah.  - No, you didn't.
有的时候让他们离我们远点的唯一办法就是
Sometimes the only way to keep them off is to throw the kid
往海里扔个小孩引开他们
directly in the ocean to distract them.
别胡说了 鲨鱼从来不成群出没
Shut up. Sharks don't even swim in schools.
他说鲨鱼不会成群出没
He says sharks don't swim in schools.
- 这孩子还挺机智的啊  - 的确
- Smart kid.  - Yeah, he is.
这么机智的孩子
A really smart kid is exactly the kind of quality meal
正是一群鲨鱼在绕着船打转的时候
a humongous school of sharks
所寻找的高水准大餐
is looking for when they're circling a boat.
李叔叔 你够了
Oh, Uncle Lee, shut up.
鱼上钩了 收线 收线 收线
Hey, you got a strike! Strike, strike, strike!
轻点拽 小心你的拇指
Ease up on the drag, and watch your fuckin' thumb!
- 你有鱼上钩了  - 天啊 别打我
- You got a strike now!  - Jesus! Don't hit me!
- 不准说脏话  - 他有鱼上钩了
- No swearing!  - He got a strike!
- 放松点  - 我能搞得定 我们搞得定
- Ease up on it.  - I got it! We got it!
开你的船去 管好你自己的事
Drive the boat! Mind your business!
- 你得把鱼钩住  - 是什么鱼
- You gotta get the hook in him.  - What kind of fish is it?
我们搞得定 闭嘴 管好你自己的事就行了
We're fine! Shut up! Mind your business!
- 什么鱼啊  - 大白鲨
- What kind of fish is it?  - Great white.
- 肯定是大白鲨  - 加把劲
- It's gotta be a great white.  - Come on!
- 肯定是大白鲨  - 闭嘴
- It's gotta be a great white.  - Shut up!
也有可能是梭鱼 谁知道呢
Or maybe a barracuda. Who knows?
不是鲨鱼
It's not a shark!
- 好了 拽上来  - 不是鲨鱼
- Come on, pull him up!  - It's not a shark!
- 别说了  - 拜托
- Just stop talking!  - Come on!
16号出口
松树街
曼彻斯特
距曼彻斯特木兰县的松树街还有0.5英里
那地方是怎么跟那里连接起来的
How come that's connected to those?
没有连起来 只是看起来像而已
It's not connected, it just looks that way.
我在教你认小岛呢
I'm trying to teach you the islands.
那座小岛被一个富豪买了
That's the island the rich guy bought
所以上面没有其他房子
so no one else would put a house on it.
就是那么有钱就是那么任性
That's how rich he is.
糕点师傅岛 痛苦岛
Baker island, Misery island.
我和你兰迪婶婶就是在痛苦岛上结婚的
Misery island's where me and your aunt Randi got married.
- 谁啊  - 是我
- Hello?  - Yeah, hi.
苏茜 爸爸回来了
Suzy, daddy's home.
嗨 苏茜 爸爸回来了
Hi, Suzy. Daddy's home.
- 嗨 爸爸  - 你好啊 甜心
- Hi, daddy.  - Hi, sweetheart.
抱抱
Hug.
老天 你快把我的脖子搂断了
Oh, Jesus Christ! You're breaking my neck!
李
Lee?
嗯 等一下
Yeah, hang on.
- 玩得开心吗  - 很开心
- Hey. Did you have a good time?  - Yeah, really good.
- 你妈呢  - 他们刚走
- Where's your mother?  - They just left.
不是吧
Oh, no!
是的 她也很想你
Yeah, she said missed you too.
总会有下次的 你有睡觉吗
Well, there's always next time. Did you get any sleep?
你说呢 有我妈在可“安静”了
Oh, yeah, it's so restful when my mother's here.
太糟了 嗨 小凯
Oh, too bad. Hi, Kary.
- 嗨 爸爸  - 抱抱
- Hi, daddy.  - Come here.
- 放我下来  - 我会放你下来的 放轻松
- Put me down.  - I'm putting you down. Relax.
我就是想亲亲你 宝贝 好了
I'm just giving you a kiss. Honey, all right...
小心 凯伦
Karen! Karen!
- 我差点把你一头摔到地上  - 天啊
- I almost dropped you on your head.  - Jesus.
我在做美发沙龙呢
I'm making a hair salon.
是吗 真棒
Oh, yeah? It's really good.
你想给我剪头发吗
You wanna cut my hair?
女生专属 抱歉啦
It's just for girls. I'm sorry.
没关系 我懂的 甜心
That's all right. I understand, sweetheart.
我能看看电视找找灵感吗
Can I watch TV to get some ideas?
- 不行  - 可以
- No.  - Yeah.
去吧
Go ahead.
走开啦
Get off.
天啊
Oh, god.
感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
好点了
Better.
- 是吗  - 是的
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
你听起来好点了
You sound better.
你们真的用到渔具了吗
So did you guys actually use the fishing tackle?
当然了
Oh, yeah, we really did.
小帕钓到了一条十八磅的大青鱼
Patty caught a humongous bluefish... 18 pounds.
是吗 太厉害了
Oh, yeah? Well, that's awesome.
我这辈子都没见过谁像他那么开心
Oh, I never seen anybody so happy in my whole life.
这里真棒
Its nice in here.
你把这里保持的很棒
You keep it nice.
- 家务打扫得真棒  - 滚开
- What a homemaker.  - Fuck off.
离我远点
All right. Get away from me.
别碰我
Stop it.
别这样 停下
Oh, don't. Stop.
拜托 我还病着了
Please, I'm sick.
好了 真心的 离我远点
Okay. For real, get off of me.
- 嗨 斯坦尼  - 天 别碰他
- Hi, Stanny.  - Oh, god, let him alone.
- 你怎么没哭啊  - 我刚哄好他
- How come you're not crying?  - I just got him settled.
- 你把他哄好干什么  - 李 别把他抱起来
- What are you getting him settled for?  - Lee, don't pick him up.
如果他没有哭 就让他自己一个人待着
If he's not crying, leave well enough alone.
自己一个人待着 我和你妈妈
Leave well enough alone. That's what me and your mommy
就应该这样做 而不是结婚
should have done instead of getting married.
- 闭嘴吧  - 那就没有你了
- Oh, shut up.  - Then you wouldn't be here.
也没有你的姐姐们
Your sisters wouldn't be here,
我就能在我自己的客厅
and I could watch the football
安安静静看球赛了
game in my own living room with peace and quiet.
我想说你可以去自慰了
You know what? You can go fuck yourself.
那可真浪费 嗨 小家伙
Oh, jeez waste. Hey, kiddo.
天啊 你可真帅啊 你知道吗
Oh, my gosh. You're very handsome, you know that?
看到了吗 我没把他弄哭
See that? I didn't make him cry.
抱起来放下去
Up and down.
他没有哭
He's not crying...
因为我知道怎么搞定他
'Cause I know how to handle him.
他怎么样 乔怎么样
How is he? How's Joe?
他很好 还不错
He's fine. You know, he's... he's all right.
实际上 他还过得挺不错的
Actually, he's doing all right.
你们没有把啤酒喝完吗 你们今天过得还好吗
And you didn't run out of beer? You got through the day okay?
当然了 我们可是很节制的
Oh, yeah. We were very temperate.
我就不明白你们为什么还要费劲爬上那破船
I don't know why you guys bother getting on the friggin' boat.
什么意思 我们热爱大海啊
What do you mean? We love the sea.
是吗 你们在大海上喝了多少啤酒
Oh, yeah? How many beers did you have on the sea?
- 八瓶  - 八瓶
- Eight.  - Eight?
是啊 七个小时喝了八瓶
Yep, eight, over a seven-hour period, which...
真是大开眼界啊
Wow, I am well impressed.
平均也就
...is...
每小时一点一四二八五七二瓶吧
...1.1428572 beers an hour.
几乎就和没喝一样
It's like you didn't even have anything to drink at all.
我告诉过你我会少喝的
Yeah, I told you I was cutting down.
天啊 不要 你想干什么
Oh, god, no. What do you think you're gonna do?
我想我准备去洗个澡
I guess I'm gonna take a shower.
兰迪 我向上帝发誓
Randi, I swear to god.
你真该看看他的表情
You should have seen his face.
那么开心
So happy.
和我们带着姑娘们去玩旋转木马时她们的表情一样
It was like when we took the girls on the merry-go-round.
就是纯粹的开心
I mean, it was just pure happiness.
拜托 我病了
Oh, come on, I'm sick.
我病了 我是真的真的病得很严重
I'm sick. I'm really, really, deeply sick.
连呼吸都困难
It's hard to breathe.
他不在学校 我以为学校的放学时间是…
He's not at school? I thought school left out...
- 我很确定他…  - 什么
- I'm pretty sure he would have...  - What?
抱歉 保罗 我的手机…
I'm sorry, Paul, my phone is...
- 不好意思 能再说一遍吗  - 没事
- Sorry. Say that again?  - That's all right.
我很确定他去冰球训练了
I'm pretty sure he would have left for hockey practice by now.
他进了冰球队了吗
He's on the hockey team?
是的 而且还打得很好
Yeah. Yeah, he's doing real well too.
乔怎么样 他还好吗
Hey, how's Joe doing? He gonna be okay?
他还好
Yeah, he's fine.
训练场在哪 在学校吗
Where's the practice? Is it at the school?
不 在格罗斯特附近
No, they practice at Gloucester around.
- 训练场地在…  - 不好意思
- They practice in the...  - I'm sorry.
- 不在学校吗  - 不在
- It's not at the school?  - No.
什么 不好意思
What? I'm sorry.
- 你能听到我说话吗  - 这破手机…
- Can you hear me?  - The phone is...
没事 你能听到我说话吗
That's all right. Can you hear me?
- 能听到  - 在格罗斯特
- Yes.  - It's at Gloucester, okay?
好的 我知道了
Okay. I understand.
我们和洛克波特队一起训练 但是他们是主队
We play with the Rockport team, but they're the lead team.
好的 我明白了 谢谢你 保罗
Okay, I understand. Thank you, Paul.
不客气 代我问候乔 好吗
Yeah, sure thing. Give Joe my regards, all right?
- 我会的  - 怎么了
- I will.  - What's up?
乔·钱德勒又进医院了
Uh, Joe Chandler's in the hospital again.
真可怜
Oh, how awful.
- 电话里是谁  - 李·钱德勒
- Who was on the phone?  - That was Lee Chandler.
- 李·钱德勒  - 就是那个李·钱德勒
- Lee Chandler?  - The very one.
住手
Knock it off!
钱德勒 够了
Chandler! Knock it off!
再有一次你就出局
One more time and you're out.
听到没 钱德勒 再有一次就出局
You understand that, Chandler? One more time.
- 去你的  - 你说什么
- Ah, fuck me.  - What's that?
- 去你妈的  - 你出局了
- Fuck my fuckin' ass.  - All right, you're out.
钱德勒 你被罚下了
Chandler, you're benched.
好像我在乎似的
All right. Ask me if I give a shit.
你说什么
What was that?
教练 那是他叔叔
Coach, that's his uncle.
他爸肯定又进医院了
His father must be in the hospital.
谁爸爸 钱德勒的吗
Whose father, Chandlers?
是的 他叔叔只有在他爸住院的时候才来
Yeah, he only comes around...
他有充血性心力衰竭
He's got congestive heart failure.
帕特里克的爸爸 不是帕特里克
Patrick's dad, I mean, not... not Patrick.
所以那是李·钱德勒 那个大名鼎鼎的李·钱德勒吗
So that's Lee Chandler. The Lee Chandler, huh?
是的 但是教练 你知道那些传闻是胡扯的吧
Yeah, but coach, you know that story's bullshit, right?
完全是胡扯 教练
Total bullshit, coach.
别说脏话
You guys wanna watch the language?
- 抱歉  - 抱歉
- Sorry.  - Sorry.
管好你们自己的事 好吗
All right. Mind your own business for a little while, huh?
休息一下 喝点水
Let's take a break. Get a water.
你爸出什么事了
So, uh, something going on with your dad?
他父亲今天早晨去世了
His father passed away this morning.
天哪 我很遗憾
Oh, jeez. I'm sorry to hear that. I really am.
我 听我说 想做什么就去做吧
I, uh... well, listen, do what you gotta do.
我感到很难过
I, uh... I feel terrible.
要不你进去
Why don't you, uh...
进去换一下衣服
all right, well, go in and change,
然后我们再谈这事 好吗
and we'll talk about it later, all right?
去吧 我在外面等你
Go ahead. I'll meet you outside.
- 好吧  - 好 谢谢
- All right.  - All right. Thank you.
好了 别围观了
All right, show's over.
走吧
Come on, let's go.
- 你没事吧  - 我
- You all right?  - Uh, my...
把曲棍放回去 好吗
Take your sticks back, would you?
- 我在里面等你  - 好
- Hey, I'll see you in there.  - Yeah.
- 等会聊 好吗  - 等会聊
- We'll talk, okay?  - I'll talk to you soon.
一会见 爱你
See you soon. I love you.
来集合
Line it up again.
快来
Come on, let's go.
我要去医院签一些文件
I have to go to the hospital and sign some more papers.
你想再见见他吗
Do you wanna see him?
我不知道 何必呢
I don't know. Why?
他看起来什么样
What's he look like?
看起来像死人
He looks like he's dead.
我是说 不是像睡着了之类的
I mean, he doesn't look like he's sleeping or anything.
但他看起来也不吓人
But he doesn't look gross, either.
我不知道
I don't know.
你也不必勉强
Well, you know, you don't have to.
我是想见他的
I wanted to see him.
也许你不想在记忆里留下这种画面
Maybe you don't want that image in your memory.
我不
I don't...
你自己决定
It's up to you.
你想怎么办
What do you wanna do?
想让我带你回家
You want me to take you home?
还是想让我帮你决定
Want me to decide for you?
那就走吧
Let's just go.
你他妈在做什么
What the fuck are you doing?
- 我刚刚说要进去  - 不 你说走吧
- I just said let's go inside!  - No, you said let's just go,
- 然后就要下车  - 我是说要进去
- and then you get out of the car?  - I meant let's go inside.
- 你到底怎么回事  - 你怎么回事
- What the matter with you?  - What's your problem?
- 你的腿差点就废了  - 好吧
- I could have ripped your fuckin' leg off!  - Okay, okay!
抱歉我说错话了
I'm sorry I misused the English language.
我很抱歉 李叔叔
I'm sorry, uncle Lee.
我也很抱歉 我只是有点怕
I'm sorry, too. I just get scared.
可以了 谢谢你
Yeah, okay, thank you.
不用谢
Of course.
你要打一下传呼机
You gotta hit the bleeper.
我没有传呼机
I don't have a bleeper.
我来吧 有密码
I'll do it. There's a code.
我可以请几个朋友过来吗
Hey, is it okay if I invite some of my friends over?
- 我说过我会联络他们的  - 去吧
- I told them I would call them.  - Go ahead.
可以订些披萨吗 家里没吃的了
And can we get some pizza? 'Cause there's nothing to eat here.
行
Okay.
- 你喜欢什么样的披萨  - 什么样都行
- What kind would you like?  - Any kind is fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
至少他没有经受痛苦
At least he didn't suffer.
对家人来说是坏事 但对他是好事
It's worse for the family, but it's better for the person.
他人很好 帕特里克 我是这么想的
Well, he was a fuckin' great guy, Patrick, I'll tell you that.
那是肯定的
That's for sure.
我记得那次
Yeah, I remember this one time he...
他带我们出海 好像那时六年级
he took us out in the boat, like, in sixth grade.
我记得那次
Yeah, I remember that.
他非让我们穿那些救生衣
He made us wear these life preservers.
然后我就说
And I was like, you know,
“穿不穿有什么分别呢 钱德勒先生”
"What's the difference, Mr. Chandler?
“船要是真沉了 我们怎么都会冻死”
The boat sinks in this weather, we're dead anyways."
- 我记得这个  - 然后他说
- Yeah, I remember that.  - Then he goes,
“穿救生衣是为了”
"The life jacket's to
“防止你翻下去之后 鲨鱼吃不消”
make it easy on the sharks once you go over."
真他妈机智
Fuckin' smartass, I swear to god.
他特别喜欢那些鲨鱼的笑话
Yeah, he really liked those shark jokes.
- 风趣的家伙  - 他真幽默 兄弟
- Funny guy.  - He was funny, man.
他也很温柔
Yeah, he was gentle too, you know?
和他儿子一样
Like his son.
这是星际飞船的前任船长
So there's this former starship captain, all right?
天哪 又是《星际迷航》吗
Jesus Christ! With the Star Trek again?
- 闭嘴  - 《星际迷航》烂爆了
- Will you shut the fuck up?  - Fuck you. Star Trek sucks.
- 你个弱智  - 《星际迷航》是
- You fuckin' retard.  - Star Trek's one of the classical pillars
- 现代电影的经典作之一  - 真的吗
- of modern entertainment.  - Oh, yeah?
给我讲讲《星际迷航》 让我开开窍
Tell me about Star Trek. Enlighten me, motherfucker.
- 我来告诉你  - 我跟你做朋友多久了
- I'll tell you this...  - How long have I been friends with you?
- 你还好吗  - 我没事
- How you doing, baby?  - I'm okay.
够了 不过是《星际迷航》而已
Enough is enough, okay? It's just Star Trek.
说什么呢 给我闭嘴
How dare you! Will you shut up?
去你的《星际迷航》
Fuck Star Trek.
你喜欢的所有经典科幻片
Every Sci-Fi classic film you like
- 都是基于《星际迷航》的  - 垃圾
- was based on Star Trek.  - Star Trek's bullshit.
- 先是《星际迷航》  - 弱智
- Right? Start Trek...  - Star Trek's retarded.
- 然后是《疯狂的麦克斯》  - 弱智
- Then The Road Warrior.  - Retarded.
- 然后是《黑客帝国》  - 傻叉
- Then The Matrix.  - Retarded and shit.
我喜欢《星际迷航》
I love Star Trek!
- 真的吗  - 你胆敢这样说
- Oh, yeah, do you?  - How dare you?
去问帕特里克 他也喜欢这些
Ask Patrick. He loves 'em! He loves 'em!
- 帕特里克 你觉得呢  - 去问啊
- Patrick, what do you think?  - Go ahead, ask Patrick.
真不敢相信我们现在在聊《星际迷航》
I can't believe we're talking about Star Trek right now.
- 我喜欢《星际迷航》  - 谢谢
- I like Star Trek.  - Thank you.
嗨 李叔叔
Hey, uncle Lee.
塞尔维可以在这里过夜吗
Is it okay if Sylvie sleeps over?
我爸以前总答应她留这儿
Dad always let her.
那你为什么还来问我
Then what are you asking me for?
不为什么
No reason.
谢谢
Thanks.
别人不会来问这事
Uh, not that it would come up or anything,
但她父母以为她过夜都睡在楼下
but her parents thinks she stays downstairs when she stays over.
所以万一有人来问
So if it comes up for some reason,
你就说她在楼下睡的好吗
can you just say she stayed in the downstairs room?
- 我都不认识他们  - 你认识
- I don't even know them.  - Yeah, you do.
是麦甘恩一家 弗兰克和帕特·麦甘恩
It's the Mcganns. It's Frank and Pat Mcgann.
- 那是塞尔维·麦甘恩  - 对
- Oh, that's Sylvie Mcgann?  - Yeah.
- 好吧  - 所以
- Okay.  - So...
你可以说她睡在楼下吗
Do you mind saying she stayed downstairs,
如果他们来电话的话
like, if they call or something?
好
Okay.
我是不是该教你用避孕套了
Am I supposed to tell you to use a condom?
不
No. I mean...
- 乔是不是就会这么说  - 不
- Is that what Joe would say?  - No.
我是说 是的 我们之前讨论过了
Well, I mean, yeah, we've had the discussion and everything.
- 所以  - 好吧
- So...  - Yeah, good.
如果我们弄得太大声就跟我们说
Yeah, just let me know if we're making too much noise.
好
Okay.
我开玩笑的
Just fuckin' with you.
好吧
All right.
我是不是应该打电话给我妈
Um, do you think I should call my mom
告诉她我爸的事
to tell her about dad?
- 我不这么想 小帕  - 好吧
- No, I wouldn't, Patty.  - Yeah.
我是说 没人知道她在哪
I mean, uh, nobody even knows where she is.
是啊
Yeah.
我只是好奇你的想法
Yeah, no, I was just curious what you thought.
无所谓了 晚安 李叔叔
Anyway, good night, uncle Lee.
晚安
Good night.
你不会为了漏了一个球
Are you gonna sulk all night
生一整晚的闷气吧
long because you dropped the goddamn ball?
- 我没有生闷气  - 闭嘴吧
- I'm not sulking.  - Oh, shut up.
如果你肯用棒球手套
If you'd use a goddamn baseball mitt,
就不会漏掉这球了
you wouldn't drop the fuckin' ball.
我不需要棒球手套 我空手接的更稳
I don't need a baseball mitt! I catch better without one.
闭嘴 喂 伊莉斯
Hey, shut up. Hey, Elise!
糟透了
Oh, shit.
李 你能把小帕带上楼
Come on. Hey, Lee, you wanna take Patty upstairs
给他洗个澡吗
and get him washed up?
- 来吧 孩子  - 快上去
- Come on, kid.  - Go on, now.
没事的 我等会就上去
It'll be all right. I'll be up in a minute.
上楼吧 小帕 没事的
Go on upstairs, Patty. Everything will be okay.
我觉得你那球漏的不错
I thought it was wonderful how you dropped that ball.
- 好吧  - 我没想让你接住那球的
- Okay.  - I didn't want you to catch it.
烦死了
Oh, shit.
接着叫吧
Go on.
看在上帝的份上
Fuck's sake.
闭嘴吧
Shut the fuck up.
收件：妈妈
主题：爸爸
亲爱的妈妈
收件：妈妈
主题：爸爸
亲爱的妈妈
我写信来是要告诉你
请转贝弗利 麻省 加拉赫殡仪馆
Beverly, Massachusetts, Gallagher funeral home, please.
早上好
Morning.
你好 我是李·钱德勒
Yes, hi, my name is Lee Chandler.
我哥哥约瑟夫·钱德勒在
My brother, Joseph Chandler, is at the Beverly...
贝弗利医院的太平间 我想知道
Hospital morgue. I'm wondering, uh,
我需要找谁预约
who I need to talk to about making arrangements?
好的 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
是的
Yes.
是的 我刚刚说了
Yes, I just spoke...
是的 我是李·钱德勒
yes, my name is Lee Chandler.
我哥哥在贝弗利医院的太平间
My brother is at the Beverly hospital morgue.
是的
Yes.
好
Okay.
我明白
I understand, I'm...
我是想问问我下一步
I'm calling to find out exactly what I need to do
具体要怎么完成预约
to make arrangements for the next step.
我知道了 谢谢
I see. Okay, thank you.
可以给我张餐巾吗
Can I have a napkin?
是的
Yes.
没错 所以我要怎么
That's right, so... but what do I gotta do to get his...
把他的尸体运到
to get his body over the...
打扰一下 钱德勒先生
Excuse me, Mr. Chandler,
我觉得帕特里克不必待在这里听这些
I don't think Patrick needs to be here for this.
别这样 我没事
Don't... I'm all right.
我明白 为什么把他的尸体
I understand. So why is it more
运到曼彻斯特就贵些
to drive his body to Manchester?
所以开七分钟的高速
So you gotta take the highway
就收费贵一些吗
for seven minutes, that's why it costs more?
那灵车走一二七号公路要多少钱
Well, what does it cost for the hearse to take 127?
天哪 他关注的就是这个
Jesus, like, that's his focus?
我没事的
Jeez, I'm all right.
[曼彻斯特·艾塞克斯中学]
谢谢 李叔叔
Thanks, uncle Lee.
不客气
You're welcome.
- 谢谢 钱德勒先生  - 不客气
- Thanks, Mr. Chandler.  - You're welcome.
这样吧
So...
我们不会计较骂人的事
We're gonna forget about the language.
也不会计较打架的事
We're gonna forget about the fists.
但我希望你这几天休息一下
But I want you to take a few days off of practice.
我不想让你上冰训练
I don't want you on the ice.
说真的 先生
Well, to tell you the honest truth, sir,
我觉得那样能帮我分散注意力
I could really use the distraction.
冰上训练不是用来分散注意力的
The ice is not a distraction.
你在冰上的时候 就要专注
When you're on the ice, you gotta be there.
休息几天吧
Okay, so take a couple days off,
然后我们再聊
and we'll talk.
听我说
Listen.
在你这么大的时候 我也失去了父亲
When I was your age, I lost my dad, too.
所以…
So...
我能体会你的心情
I know what you're... you're goin' through.
如果你想来聊一聊
If you want to come in and talk,
找人讲讲心里话
or want somebody to spill your guts to,
或者就是闲聊
or throw the bull around,
我随时欢迎
the door's open.
你介意我开音乐吗
You mind if I put some music on?
开吧
No.
现在是五四…
It's at 54...
你喜欢这帮人吗
Do you like these guys?
主吉他有点弱
The lead guitar is weak,
但其他的都很棒
but otherwise they're pretty good.
我听不出什么差别
Oh, they all sound the same to me.
我们去哪
Where are we goin'?
去见律师
Gotta go to the lawyer.
做什么
What for?
听他读你父亲的遗嘱
To read your father's will.
我一定要在场吗
Do I have to be there?
我不觉得 但你应该去
I don't think so, but I think you're supposed to be.
你觉得他会把船留给谁
Who do you think he left the boat to?
他肯定会把所有东西留给你
I'm sure he left you everything.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你对哪里不明白
Which, uh, part are you having trouble with?
我不可能做他的监护人
Well, I can't be the guardian.
我是说 我做不了
I mean, I can't.
我还以为乔已经
Well, naturally, I... I assumed Joe had
跟你商量过这件事了
discussed all this with you.
没有
No.
他没说过
He didn't.
没有
No.
我…
Uh, I... I...
对不起 我很惊讶
sorry, I have to say, I'm somewhat taken aback.
他不可能和我一起住 我只有一间房间
He can't live with me. I live in one room.
但乔已经准备好了帕特里克的抚养费
Well, but Joe has provided for Patrick's upkeep.
供他吃穿等等
Food, clothes, etcetera.
而且房子和船都完全是个人所有的
And the house and the boat are owned outright.
我不可能每天往返波士顿
I can't commute from Boston every day
直到他十八岁
until he turns 18.
我觉得他是想让你换个地方住
I think the idea was that you would relocate.
换…换到那里
R... relocate to where?
- 你看…  - 这里
- Well, you look...  - Here?
你的哥哥
Well, as you can see, your brother
已经把所有事情打点好了
worked everything out extremely carefully.
- 但他不可能  - 就是那样的
- But he can't have...  - Yes.
他不可能是那个意思
He can't have meant that.
他准备了五千美元
Uh, he's allowed up to $5,000
用作你的搬家费用
to pay for moving expenses.
还有一小笔钱
And there's, uh... there's also a small amount
是留作
set aside for, uh, you know,
你安顿好之前的个人收入
for you to draw from as personal income while you settle in.
如果你同意当监护人的话
I mean, assuming...that you accept.
我的叔叔唐尼和姨妈特丽莎呢
What about my uncle Donny and aunt Teresa?
乔不觉得帕特里克和他们关系特别
Joe didn't feel that Patrick really had any special relationship
- 或者很亲近  - 我不明白
- or feeling about them.  - I don't understand.
而且现在 我觉得你知道
And now, as I think you know,
他们搬去了威斯康辛
they've moved out to Wisconsin, I believe.
明尼苏达
Minnesota.
- 明尼苏达  - 明尼苏达的明内通卡
- Minnesota.  - Minnetonka, Minnesota.
没错
That's right.
我记得这些年你在这里住过不少时候
It was my impression that you'd spent a lot of time here over the years.
我只是来帮帮忙
I was just the back up.
过来照顾一下小帕
I came up here to look after Patty, yeah,
如果乔进医院的话 我父亲已经不在了
if Joe was in the hospital after my father couldn't do it,
但我们…
but we...
应该是唐尼才对
it was supposed to be Donny.
我只是帮下忙
I'm just the back up.
我只能说我…
Well, I... I can just repeat that I'm... I'm...
我很惊讶乔没有跟你说这件事
astonished that Joe didn't run this by you,
他是个很仔细的人
thorough as he was.
因为他知道我会怎么回答他
Yeah, 'cause he knew what I would say if he would have asked.
就一次 就那一次
Once! It was once!
一次而已没什么大不了
Oh, one time nothin'. It's nothin' but one time.
别打这半边 你就不会哭着回家
Stay out of this quadrant, and you won't go home in tears.
好吧
All right.
声音小一点 你们这群蠢货
You wanna keep it down, you fuckin' morons?
我的孩子们在睡觉
My kids are sleepin'.
对不起 我不知道我们有那么吵
I'm so sorry. I am... I didn't think we were that loud.
李 你能把这群蠢货
Lee. You wanna get these fuckin' pinheads
弄出我的房子吗
out of my house, please?
好 我会的
Yeah, I do.
兰迪 我真的会的
Randi, I really do.
她不该那样跟我们说话
She can't talk to us that way.
没错
Yeah.
我可不是说着玩的
I'm not fuckin' around!
现在可是凌晨两点了
It's two o'clock in the fuckin' morning.
让这帮混蛋穿好衣服
Get these fuckin' assholes dressed,
滚出去
and get 'em the fuck out of here!
我们都穿着呢
We are dressed.
她不是这个意思 她会道歉的
She didn't mean it. She'll apologize later.
你们该走了
Gotta get out of here, man.
- 回见  - 好的
- See ya later.  - Right on.
李
Lee.
- 谢了兄弟 小心点  - 好的
- Thanks, bro. Take care!  - All right!
- 告诉兰迪我们很抱歉  - 晚安
- Tell Randi we're sorry.  - Good night!
- 喝酒就别开车了  - 我们很抱歉
- Don't drink and drive.  - We're so sorry!
你看见木星了吗
You see Jupiter?
注意看路
Hold on. Keep your eyes on the road!
汤米
Hey, Tommy!
晚安 乔
Good night, Joe!
再次说声抱歉
Sorry again!
往前 看木星 你个笨蛋
Go ahead. It's Jupiter, you fuckin' idiot.
看 那有北极星
Look at, there's the north star right there.
- 就在那  - 在哪
- Right there.  - Where?
正北方
It's... it's due north.
我早上会打扫干净的
I'll clean up in the morning.
你看见木星了 你个笨蛋
You see Jupiter, you fuckin' asshole?
拜托
Come on.
滚蛋
Fuck you.
别这样
Come on.
李
Lee.
李 没人能理解你的经历
Lee, nobody can appreciate what you've been through.
原谅我这样说
If I can say that.
如果你真的觉得你做不了监护人
And if you really feel like you can't take this on,
那是…
well, that's... that's...
那是你的权利
you know, that's your right.
- 明显地  - 那谁会做他的监护人
- Obviously.  - So who would get him?
帕特里克 要我给你买罐苏打之类的吗
Patrick, can I get you a can of soda or anything?
不用了 谢谢
No, thank you.
我不知道帕特里克的妈妈怎么了
Well, I don't know what's happening with Patrick's mother.
- 不  - 我不知道她在哪
- No.  - I'm not sure where she is,
- 也不知道她现在的情况  - 不
- or what kind of condition she's in.  - No.
不能那样
We can't do that.
天啊 不
God, no! Oh, god!
弗雷德 弗雷德 我的孩子在里面
Fred! Fred! My kids are in there!
我的孩子在里面
My kids are in there!
天啊 我要进去
God! Oh, god! I gotta go in there.
[曼彻斯特]
[消防救援]
李
Look, Lee.
你为什么不…
Why don't you just...
我该…保持联系
I'm gonna... I'll be in touch.
我在这
Um, I'm here.
[警察局]
我们之前玩得很嗨
Well, we were partying pretty hard.
喝了酒
And there was beer.
有人在分大麻
And someone was passin' around a joint,
还有可卡因
and there was cocaine.
可卡因
Cocaine?
对
Yes.
好的 继续
Okay, go ahead.
我们的卧室在楼下
Uh, anyway, our bedroom is in the downstairs,
孩子们在楼上睡觉
and the kids sleep upstairs,
大概两点的时候兰迪把大家赶走了
so Randi makes everyone leave around 2:00.
或者是三点
Or 3 A.M.
然后
And then...
她回去睡觉了
She goes back to bed.
我就上楼看了看孩子们
So I go upstairs to check on the kids,
楼上特别冷
and it's fuckin' freezin' upstairs,
但我不能开暖气
but I can't use the central heat
那会让兰迪的鼻子很干
'cause it dries out randi's sinuses,
而且她的头会很疼
and gives her really bad headaches.
所以我下楼在壁炉里生了火
So I go downstairs and I put a fire in the fireplace,
坐着看电视
and sit down and watch TV,
但是啤酒喝完了
but there's no more beer.
我还是兴奋地上蹿下跳 像个大野兔
I'm still jumpin' around like... a jackrabbit,
所以我又往炉子里加了几根木头
so I put a couple of fire logs in the fire,
我只是希望我走了房子里能暖和起来
and I... just to warm up the house while I was gone.
然后我就去小店了
And then I... I'm goin' to the mini mart,
不过我嗨过头了 不想开车
but I'm too wasted and I don't want to drive.
我是走过去的 来回大概各要二十分钟
So I walk, it's about 20 minutes each way.
走在半路上的时候
I'm about halfway there,
我发现我不记得有没有把防火板放回去了
and I can't remember if I put a screen on the fireplace.
但我觉得没什么关系
I figure it's okay.
就继续往商店走了
So I just keep goin' to the store.
就这些
And, uh, that's it.
木头一定是滚到了地板上
Log must have rolled out onto the floor.
消防员说他们把兰迪救出来了
Uh, fireman said they pulled Randi out.
她在楼下昏了过去
She's passed out downstairs.
然后…
And, uh...
然后炉子就炸了
and then the furnace blew,
他们没能再次进去
and they couldn't go back in again.
我就记得这些了
And...that's all I remember.
好的 李 现在就这样
Okay, Lee, that's all for now.
如果有其他事情
We'll... we'll call you if anything else comes up
我们会再找你问的
we want to ask you about.
如果取证结果能证明你的清白的话
Assuming the forensics bear you out,
我觉得应该没什么问题
which I'm assuming they will.
那么 就这样吗
So, uh, that's it?
李 你犯了一个大错
Look, Lee, you made a horrible mistake.
每个人都会犯错
Like a million other people did last night.
不会因为犯错就严惩你的
Not gonna crucify you.
忘了火炉上的防护网可不是什么大罪
It's not a crime to forget to put the screen on the fireplace.
我的意思是
Well, I mean, you know,
我可以走了
so I can go?
如果没什么我们还应该知道的
Well, if something comes up we don't already know about,
是的
yeah.
需要送你回家吗
You got anyone to give you a ride back home?
乔在吗 你父亲在这里吗
Is Joe here? Is your dad here?
是的
Yeah.
- 抱歉  - 好吧
- Sorry.  - Okay.
儿子
Son!
放下枪 放下
Put it down. Put it down!
趴在地上 趴下
Get on the ground. Get on the ground.
- 拜托  - 冷静 冷静
- Ah, please!  - Settle down. Settle down.
- 我们现在得把你铐上  - 趴着别动
- We need some cuffs right now.  - Stay down.
- 别动  - 把他放倒
- Stay down.  - Down, down, get him down.
好了 我们走
All right, let's go.
再见
Bye.
我们去哪儿 孤儿院吗
Where we goin', to the orphanage?
- 闭嘴  - 我做什么了
- Shut up.  - What the hell did I do?
安静点
Just be quiet.
我们有很多事情要做
All right, we got a lot to do.
船怎么办
What about the boat?
我们可以跟乔治谈谈 如果没人使用
We can talk to George about it. There's no use hangin' onto it
- 留着它没什么用  - 我会用它的
- if no one's gonna use it.  - I'm gonna use it.
- 它还需要保养  - 我会给它保养的
- It's gotta be maintained.  - I'm maintaining it.
- 我会保养它的  - 你自己可办不到
- I'm gonna maintain it.  - You can't maintain it by yourself.
怎么不行 现在船是我的 对吗
Why not? It's my boat now, isn't it?
因为你还未成年 所以你不能独自把它开出去
'Cause you're a minor, you can't take it out alone.
我…我是托管人
I'm... I'm the trustee.
- 我会来付钱  - 托管人是什么意思
- I gotta make the payments...  - What does trustee mean?
我会一直负责监管
I gotta keep up the inspections.
就是说我会处理所有事直到你…
It means I'm in charge of handling everything for you until...
就是说即使我不同意
Does that mean you're allowed
- 你也有权把船卖掉吗  - 直到你满十八岁
- to sell the boat if I don't want you to?  - Until you turn 18.
我也不确定
I don't know.
我会考虑卖船的
I'll definitely consider it.
他妈的不行
No fuckin' way.
你过于自信了
You're so goddamn sure of yourself.
没人能开船 你才十六岁
There's no one to run it. You're 16 years old.
我今年就拿驾照
I get my license this year.
没所谓 你还是未成年
Doesn't matter, you're still a minor.
你不能独自驾驶商用船只
You can't run a commercial vessel by yourself.
同时 费用也不少
Meanwhile, it's a big fuckin' expense,
这些都得我负责
and I'm the one that's gotta manage it,
- 而且我还不在这里  - 谁他妈在乎你在哪里
- and I'm not gonna be here.  - Who gives a fuck where you are?
小帕 我发誓我会狠狠教训你的
Patty, I swear to god, I'm gonna knock your fuckin' block off.
- 孩子教得不错  - 什么 你说什么
- Great parenting.  - What? What'd you say?
- 我说你把孩子教得不错  - 去你妈的
- I said great parenting.  - Fuck you!
没他妈的多管闲事 你这个傻逼
Mind your fuckin' business, you fuckin' asshole!
你往我脸上打啊
You're gonna smash me in the face.
没事了 没事了
Hey, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
- 没事了  - 你他妈想让我打你脸
- It's okay, it's okay.  - You want me to smash your fuckin' face,
- 你个傻逼  - 没事了
- you fuckin' asshole.  - It's okay. It's okay.
谢谢 没事了
Thank you. Thank you. It's okay.
李叔叔 你不是有毛病
Uncle Lee, are you fundamentally unsound?
快他妈的上车
Get in the fuckin' car.
你不开锁我怎么上车
Can't obey your orders until you unlock the door.
闭嘴
Shut up.
这引擎不会马上报废
It's not like the motor's gonna die tomorrow,
但是乔说它总是出问题
but Joe said it keeps breakin' down like a son of a bitch.
是啊 但是我们会检查一下
Yeah, but we were gonna take a look...
今天有个遗产分配的事情
see, there's an allotment of some kind, but...
但我们周末会有时间看看的
take a look this weekend.
还有些事情没定下来
Things are a little bit up in the air.
我不是那个意思
No, I... I can take care of it
如果只是常规保养 我可以帮忙照看它
as far as the general maintenance is concerned,
但是引擎说不定什么时候就不行了
but that motor's gonna go at some point.
我来照看它
I'm taking care of it.
没有买新引擎的钱
There's no allotment for a new motor.
除非 乔治你知道谁想买下它
Unless, George, you know someone who wants to buy it.
等一下 我不想把它卖掉
Wait a second, I'm not selling it.
不管怎样 我们会住在波士顿
We're gonna be in Boston, anyway.
什么
What?!
我们什么时候说要去波士顿了
Since when are we supposed to be in Boston?
别激动
Just take it easy.
不管你做什么决定
Well, whatever you decide,
船在这放着都会把你们口袋掏空的
it's gonna bleed you dry just sittin' here.
我们还不清楚最终怎样决定
Well, we don't know exactly what we're doin'.
如果他周末想回来
Well, you know, he can always stay with us
可以住在我们家
if he wants to come up weekends.
你想成为他的监护人吗
Do you want to be his guardian?
- 我们已经…  - 他不想当我的监护人
- Well, we already...  - He doesn't want to be my guardian,
- 看在上帝的份上  - 我们还打算少几个孩子呢
- for Christ sakes.  - We're tryin' to lose some kids at this point.
你见过他的房子吗
Have you seen his house?
- 是的  - 不 我们想把程序搞清楚
- Yeah.  - No, we're tryin' to work out the logistics,
- 所以我不知道…  - 我们家太挤了
- so I don't know...  - We're jammed in there pretty good,
- 但是我们…  - 上帝啊 你能闭嘴吗
- but we...  - Jesus Christ, will you stop?
如果他愿意的话 总是可以睡我们的沙发的
We've always got a sofa for him any time he wants.
- 乔治  - 你知道 对吗
- George...  - You know that, right?
好吧 我是知道
That's all right, I know... I know that.
- 我们随时欢迎他来  - 我明白
- He's welcome any time.  - I understand.
我明白 谢谢你
I... I know. Thank you.
你是脑残吗
Are you brain damaged?
你不能那样跟别人说话
You can't just talk to people like that.
你不想当我的监护人 我没意见
You don't want to be my guardian, that's fine with me.
不是这样的 只是程序的问题
It's not that, it's just the logistics.
我发誓会搞清楚的
I've just gotta work it all out, I swear.
怎么搞清楚 他们要送我去明尼苏达的
How? My takin' me to Wonkatonka, Minnesota,
- 瓦卡通卡找唐尼叔叔呢  - 明内通卡
- with uncle Donny?  - Minnetonka.
- 明尼苏达的明内通卡  - 明尼苏达的明内通卡
- Minnetonka, Minnesota.  - Okay, Minnetonka, Minnesota.
没什么不同
Same difference.
我妈妈呢
What about my mother?
什么
Huh?
法官不会同意的
The judge would never let that happen.
- 再说也没人知道她在哪里  - 我知道
- And anyway, no one even knows where she is.  - I do.
她在康涅狄格
She's in Connecticut.
至少去年的时候她在那里
At least she was last year.
你什么时候知道的
Since when do you know that?
她去年给我发过邮件
Well, she emailed me last year,
我就给她回信了
so I emailed her back.
你了解电子邮件吗
You know email?
你爸爸知道你跟她联系吗
Did your father know you were in touch with her?
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
我们能走走吗 我冷死了
Can we walk? I'm freezing.
- 我只知道…  - 我明白
- All I know is...  - I know, I know, I know.
她酗酒 她是个疯子
She's a drunk, she's insane,
她让狗在地板上拉屎
she let the dog shit on the floor.
你爸爸最不想见的
It's the last thing that your father
就是这样
ever would have wanted.
现在你倒是
Oh! Oh, like suddenly you care
在乎他的想法了
what he would have wanted.
现在去哪儿
Where to now?
- 殡仪馆  - 真好
- The funeral parlor.  - Great.
等等 我们这是去…
Whoa, whoa, whoa, where are we...
我们这是去哪儿
where are we goin'?
他在贝弗利
He's in Beverly.
曼彻斯特没有殡仪馆吗
There's no funeral homes in Manchester?
没有
Nope.
这里有墓地
The cemetery's here.
我们赶紧把这事办完吧
Let's just get this done.
往南走有很多来过冬的人
Down south, we got a lot of snowbirds.
年初时 北边的人搬去那里
Early in the year, people from the north head down there,
他们从别的地方来 然后在那里死去
they die down there, they're not from the area.
他们喜欢我们这儿什么
What do they even like about us?
- 为所爱的人做安排  - 好吧
- Makin' arrangements for a loved one.  - Right.
很多情况下 搬到这里来
A lot of times, people are comin' in,
- 就是他们最后的愿望了  - 是的
- last thing they had on their mind.  - Right.
有时候我发现家庭尽管有不和
Sometimes I find there's dysfunction in the family still,
但是大家还是会到一起来 你明白吗
somehow people come together. You know?
老兄 那个一脸严肃的人
Dude, what is with that guy
到底是怎么回事
and the big serious and somber act?
我不知道
I don't know.
不 但是认真的讲 他自己不清楚
No, but seriously, does he not realize
别人知道他每天都做同样的事吗
that people know he does this every single day?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们为什么不把他埋了
Why can't we bury him?
天冷了 地太硬了
Too cold. The ground is too hard.
春天再埋
They'll bury him in the spring.
那在春天之前他怎么办
So what do they do with him until then?
放在冷库里
Put him in a freezer.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
是的
Yes.
这把我吓到了
That really freaks me out.
没关系
It doesn't matter.
等等
Wait a minute.
Wait.
好像车停在那边 抱歉
I think I parked the car the other way. Sorry.
小型蒸汽铲怎么样
What about one of those mini steam shovels?
什么
What?
有一次我在纽黑文的墓地里
I once saw one of those mini steam shovels
见过那种小型蒸汽铲
one time in a graveyard in New Haven.
两秒钟就能挖出一个完美的坑
It's like a perfect little hole in about two seconds.
我真的不知道去哪里买
Well, I don't really know how to get a hold of one
也不知道要花多少钱
or how much it would cost.
我们为什么不能考虑一下呢
Why can't we just look into it?
因为你不能在历史悠久的
Because you can't use heavy equipment
玫瑰谷公墓里使用重型设备
in the historic Rosedale cemetery.
为什么不能
Why not?
因为那里葬着一些非常重要的人物
Because there are very important people
和他们的子孙
who are buried there,
他们都不想自己的遗体
and their descendants don't want steam shovels
被蒸汽铲打扰
vibrating over their dead bodies.
那我们为什么不把他埋在别处
Well, why can't we just bury him someplace else?
因为乔买的地方就在那里
Because that's the plot that Joe bought.
别问我为什么
Don't ask me why.
但是如果你有其他打算
But if you want to make some other arrangements,
或者想把他埋在别处
you want to find someplace else to bury him,
你得去跟殡仪馆的人谈
you want to talk to the mortician,
你还得给圣心教堂打电话
and you want to call up Sacred Heart
跟马丁神父谈谈
and talk to father Martin
看看如果改变计划的话
and find out how much that's gonna cost
要花多少钱
and make all those arrangements,
随便你 否则的话 就按现在的来
be my guest. Otherwise, let's just leave it.
我只是不喜欢让他躺在尸体冷藏柜
I just don't like him being in a freezer.
没错
Yeah.
我也不喜欢
I don't like it, either,
但那并不是他 因为他已经去世了
but it isn't him because he's gone.
那只是他的躯体
It's just his body.
我只想说我被吓到了
I'm just saying it kind of freaks me out.
该死 我把车停哪了
Oh, god damn it, where did I park the car?
我不知道 但我希望你赶快弄清楚
Yeah, I don't know, but I wish you'd figure it out
因为我快冻死了
because I'm freezing my ass off.
你没有正常点的棉衣吗
You don't have a normal winter coat?
- 没有吗  - 有 我有
- Huh?  - Yeah. Yeah, I do.
你怎么不戴有指头的手套
Why don't you wear gloves with the real fingers on them?
我的天
Oh, god, fuck.
我把该死的车停哪去了
Oh, fuck, where did I park this motherfucking car?
该死 太冷了
God damn, it's cold.
为什么 怎么不穿你的羽绒服
Why? What's the matter with your winter jacket?
- 你认真的 小帕  - 把暖气打开
- Seriously, Patty?  - Just turn the heat on.
已经打开了
It's on already.
调高一点
Well, turn it up a little.
已经调到最大了
It's all the way up.
这吹的是冷气
It's blowing freezing air on me.
它需要预热一下
It just needs a minute to warm up.
你哪一年买的 一九二八年吗
What year did you get this thing, 1928?
那时候是不是还给你带了匹马
Where's the horse that goes with this fucking car?
说不定它现在还能哈气
Maybe he can breathe on us.
小帕 我对天发誓
Patty, I swear to god.
我知道 为什么不让我爸在那地方
I know. Why don't we keep my dad in here
再待上三个月
for the next three months?
能省好一笔钱
We'd save a fucking fortune.
你能对尸体冷藏柜的事消停会吗
Would you shut the fuck up about the freezer?
因为殡仪员和葬礼的事
Want me to have a nervous breakdown
想把我逼疯吗
because there's undertakers and a funeral?
- 谁在意  - 不 我不会
- Who cares?  - No. I don't.
暖和起来了
Okay, it's getting warmer.
我有个乐队排练 能载我回趟家
I got band practice. Can you drive me home
拿下我的东西
so I can get my stuff
然后送我去我女朋友家吗
and take me over to my girlfriend's house?
可以
Sure.
是来家过夜的那个女孩吗
This the same girl who was over at the house?
不是 那天是塞尔维 今天是桑迪
No. That was Sylvie, and this is Sandy.
她们还不知道彼此的事
They don't know about each other,
所以什么都别说
so, uh, please don't say anything
以免露馅
in case it comes up.
我不会说的
I won't.
你真和这些女孩发生性行为了吗
Do you actually have sex with these girls?
我们总不能只玩电脑游戏吧
We don't just play computer games.
和她们俩都做过吗
With both of them?
桑迪妈妈在家
Well, with Sandy's mom here,
现在还属于小偷小摸阶段
it's sort of, uh, strictly just like basement business.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是我还在努力实现中
It means I'm working on it.
停 奥托 你在干嘛
Stop. Otto, man, what are you doing?
我怎么了
What did I do?
你没跟上节拍 伙计
You're way behind, man.
我没有
No, I'm not.
你有点没跟上 奥托
You're a little behind, Otto.
你得跟着贝斯的节奏来 奥托
You got to start with the bass, Otto.
伙计 跟着我 好吗
Come on, man, just stay with me, all right?
- 来吧  - 好 不好意思
- Let's go.  - All right, I'm sorry.
没事 来吧
All right. Yeah. Come on.
没事
It's all right.
来吧
Come on, let's go.
- 开始了 伙计们  - 再来一次
- All right, guys.  - Let's go again.
奥托 怎么样
Otto, you good?
- 你好了吗 伙计  - 开始了 伙计
- You good, buddy?  - Let's go, baby.
我来起头
Let me ask stentorian.
一 二 三
1, 2, 3.
你好 你是李吗
Hi. Are you Lee?
我叫吉尔 桑迪的妈妈
I'm Jill, Sandy's mom.
我想他们快结束了
I think they're wrapping up.
你想进来喝杯啤酒什么的吗
You want to come inside and have a beer or something?
不用了 谢谢
It's all right. Thank you.
我想表达我对乔的哀悼
I wanted to offer my condolences about Joe.
他是个了不起的家伙
He was a terrific guy.
像他这样的人很少
There's not too many like him.
他是个了不起的父亲
He was a wonderful father.
谢谢
Thank you.
我 我问一下帕特里克
I was... I was going to ask Patrick
看他想不想留下来吃晚饭
if he wants to stay for supper,
如果你觉得没问题的话
if that's okay with you.
你要一起来吗 我做的有点多
You want to join us? I made way too much.
不用了
That's all right.
我过会再来接他
I'll just come back and get him.
我该几点过来
What time should I come back?
我不知道 九点 九点半
Oh, I don't know. 9, 9:30.
据说他们还要一起“写作业”
They're going to do their homework together, supposedly.
那好吧 我九点半过来
All right. I'll come back at 9:30.
好 若你十分钟内改变主意了
Okay. When you change your mind in the next ten minutes,
我们就在里面
we're right inside.
好 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
我的天 你怎么解开这个
Jesus Christ, how do you unbuckle this?
我指节上的皮都蹭掉了
I'm scraping the skin off my knuckles.
等等 把你手拿出来
Hold on. Just take your hand out.
你能先把你手从我的私处拿出来吗
Would you please just take your hand out of my cunt?
好 好
Okay. Okay.
我们要把裤子都脱了吗
Oh, are we taking our pants off?
我要把我的裤子脱了
I'm taking my pants off.
我不知道你在干吗
I don't know what you're doing.
我要把我的裤子脱了
I'm taking my pants off.
快点
Come on.
你得先把你的鞋脱了
You got to take your shoe off first.
- 我的天  - 我在脱了
- Jesus.  - I'm... I'm trying.
孩子们 出来 吃晚饭了
Hey, kids, come on, have some dinner.
好的 妈妈 我们马上下去
Thanks, mom. We'll be right down.
好的 吉尔 等一下
Thanks, Jill. One second.
我准备退出登录了
I just got to log off.
你闭嘴好吗 她又不是弱智
Would you shut up? She's not retarded.
你为什么老找我茬
Why are you picking on me?
我没有找你茬
I'm not picking on you.
你会让我惹上麻烦的
You'll get me in trouble.
我们不会惹上麻烦的
We're not gonna get in trouble.
我们会
We are.
我不敢相信你能做出什么
I can't believe what you're gonna do.
数学作业做的怎么样了
How's the math homework?
挺好的
It's good.
非常令人沮丧
Very frustrating.
那就好
Good.
那些算法就是个磨人的小妖精
Those algorithms are a bitch.
真的很好吃 吉尔
This is really good, Jill.
- 谢谢 帕特里克  - 这是
- Thank you, Patrick.  - Is this a...
这是自制卡本纳拉奶油培根酱吗
this is a homemade carbonara sauce?
我的天 闭嘴吧
Jesus, shut up.
不是
No.
你在唬我对吧
You could have fooled me.
我的天
Jesus.
怎么了
What? What?
你真是个马屁精
You're such a kiss-ass.
- 桑迪  - 怎么了
- Sandy!  - What,
因为我大加赞赏你母亲的厨艺吗
because I appreciate your mother's cooking?
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Good night.  - Good night.
你不想知道发生了什么吗
Aren't you going to ask what happened?
- 我不想知道  - 我猜也是
- I don't want to know.  - Guess not.
国家冰上曲棍球联盟
圣路易斯蓝调队 VS 波士顿棕熊队
2 : 2
决胜点球
加油
Come on.
你好
Hello.
你好 是李吗
Hello. Lee?
我是兰迪
It's Randi.
- 人呢  - 不好意思 我在
- Hello?  - Yeah. Sorry. I'm here.
- 你好吗  - 不错 你呢
- Hi. How are you?  - Okay. How are you?
- 挺好的  - 那就好
- Good.  - Good.
我打电话来是因为
I was just calling...
乔治告诉我乔的事了
George told me about Joe,
我只是想打个电话慰问一下
and I just wanted to call and say I'm sorry.
希望我没打扰到你
I hope you don't mind me calling.
没有 我很好 谢谢
No. It's fine. Thank you.
我不介意 你怎么样
I don't mind. How are you?
现在感觉不怎么好
Not so good right now.
我想我们本应该注意到的
I guess we should have seen it coming,
但这始终让人难以接受
but it's still hard to believe.
- 没错  - 是的
- Yeah.  - Yeah.
- 帕特里克怎么样  - 他挺好的
- How's Patrick doing?  - He's good.
除了流露出来的情感外 当然了
Beyond the obvious, obviously.
他挺好的 我不太清楚
He's okay. He's fine. I don't know.
你知道那些孩子 很难看出心事
You know how kids are. It's hard to tell.
他也没对我坦诚相待
He doesn't really open up with me,
但他看起来不错 他有许多的朋友
but he seems fine. He's got a lot of friends.
- 那就好  - 没错
- Oh, well, that's good.  - Yeah, it is.
我不知道你开始准备后事了没
So I don't know if you'd planned a service yet,
但我想问一下希望你不要介意
but I was also going to ask, if you wouldn't mind,
如果你没问题的话我想过来一趟
I'd like to be there if it's okay with you.
没事 我不介意
Yeah, it's fine. I don't mind.
好 谢谢
Okay, okay. Thank you.
这对我真的很重要
It would mean a lot to me.
不 你应该过来
No, you should come.
我会告诉你具体的时间
I'll let you know when it's going to be.
谢谢
Thank you.
我能问一下
So can I ask, uh...
你最近怎么样
How are you?
我不知道 你呢
I don't know. How are you?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们现在挺不错的
We're doing pretty well.
我应该告诉你
I should probably tell you.
我准备
I'm going to be a...
事实上 我怀孕了
actually, I'm... I'm pregnant.
- 是吗  - 是的
- Oh, yeah?  - Yeah.
准备要生了
You know, like, ready to pop.
我还不知道这事
Oh, I didn't know that.
我不知道该不该告诉你
Uh, I didn't know if I should tell you,
但是
but...
没事 恭喜你
No, it's fine. Congratulations.
谢谢 等你见到我时
Thank you. You would probably decide it for yourself
你就明白了
when you see me.
好吧
Yeah.
那么
So, uh, you know,
我想说
I just wanted to say, you know...
事实上 不好意思
actually, uh, I... oh, sorry.
我不是有意要打断你 我得挂了
I didn't mean to cut you off. I just got to go.
我只是想确定一下我和乔希
I just wanted to make sure it's okay
出席葬礼没问题吧
if me and Josh come to the funeral.
- 完全没问题  - 谢谢你 李
- It's totally okay.  - Thank you, Lee.
好的 上帝保佑
Okay. God bless.
- 再见  - 拜拜
- So long.  - Bye.
你在开玩笑吗 我从没去过波士顿
Are you kidding me? I've never even been to Boston.
你还撑得住吗
So how are you holding up?
怎么了
What's the matter?
我说你还撑得住吗
I said how are you holding up?
这问题问得很蠢 来点吃的吗
It's a stupid question. Get some food?
我吃了点奶酪
Oh, uh, I had some cheese.
你吃了点奶酪 混蛋
You had some cheese, asshole?
我给你拿点吃的
I'll get you something.
- 我什么也不想吃  - 亚尼内
- I don't want anything.  - Hey, Janine!
- 确定吗  - 什么
- Sure?  - What?
- 我什么都不想吃  - 没事
- I don't want anything.  - Never mind.
- 什么  - 算了 忽略我
- What?  - Forget it. Skip it.
你说的我什么都听不到
I can't hear a goddamn word you're saying.
什么
What?
李吃过东西了吗
Did Lee get food?
他没有 什么
He didn't... what?
李吃过东西了吗
Did Lee get food?
没有 他不想吃
No! He doesn't want any.
- 我们没事  - 我给他搞一盘
- We're good.  - I'll make him a plate.
算了 他不想
Forget it. He doesn't...
我们没事
We're fine.
他不想要
He doesn't want any...
我让塞尔维过来可以吗
Hey, is it okay if I invite Sylvie over?
她是哪个
Which one is she?
她是 头发是棕色的那个
She's the one with the... The brown hair.
不行
No.
什么叫不行
What do you mean, no?
我不喜欢她
I don't like her.
我现在不想她在家里
I don't want her in the house right now.
为什么不行 你又不用和她讲话
Why not? You don't even have to talk to her.
对不起 去她家或者打给你朋友
Sorry. Go to her house or call one of your friends.
就这样
That's that.
我去你那边你妈妈没关系吗
Would it be cool with your mom if I came over there?
我莫名其妙
I have no idea.
好 明天跟你说
Okay. I'll talk to you tomorrow.
我也不能呆在她那边
Well, I can't stay there, either.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
你要呆这儿
You going to stay in here?
不行吗
Yeah. Why not?
我以为你想呆在爸爸的房间里
I thought maybe you'd want to stay in dad's room.
为什么 你想我去那间
Hmm? Why, do you want me to?
不是 只是那房间更好
No. It's just a better room.
他也没在用
And he's not using it.
好 我去那间房间
Okay. I'll stay in there.
反正我们也不会在这里呆很久的
We're not gonna be here that much longer anyway.
我们不会搬到波士顿去的 李叔叔
We're not moving to Boston, uncle Lee.
现在我不想讨论这个话题
Well, I don't want to talk about that right now.
你说他给你留了搬家的钱
You said he left you money so you could move.
这不意味着
Yeah. That doesn't mean...
不管怎样 波士顿有什么呢
Anyway, what's in Boston?
你是个清洁工
You're a janitor.
- 那又怎样  - 你在哪都能做
- So what?  - You can do that anywhere.
小镇上多的是厕所
There's plenty of toilets
和堵住的排水管
and clogged-up drains all over town.
- 我不想  - 我所有的朋友都在这里
- I don't want to...  - All my friends are here.
我在冰球队里
I'm on the hockey team.
我在篮球队里
I'm on the basketball team.
我现在得保住我们的船
I got to maintain our boat now.
我每周两天在乔治的船上工作
I work on George's boat two days a week.
我有两个女朋友
I got two girlfriends,
而且我还有个乐队
and I'm in a band.
你是昆西的一个清洁工
You're a janitor in Quincy.
在哪生活你有什么好在意的
What the hell do you care where you live?
我要睡了
I got to go to sleep.
晚安
Good night.
你今晚住哪
Where are you going to stay tonight?
我不知道 汽车旅馆吧
I don't know. A motel.
你什么时候给我打电话
What time you going to call me?
等我到旅馆
When I get to the motel.
我想九点前接到你的消息
I want to hear from you by 9:00,
不然我就报警
or I'm going to call the cops.
- 知道了吗  - 好的好的
- Understand?  - Yes. Yes.
帕特里克 过来和你李叔叔说再见
Patrick, come say goodbye to your uncle Lee!
- 没关系  - 有关系
- It's okay.  - No, it's not.
帕特里克
Patrick!
来了
Coming!
我会来看他的
I'm going to see him.
再见 李叔叔
Bye, uncle Lee.
再见
So long.
小帕
Patty?
我觉得自己不对劲
I think there's something wrong with me.
什么意思 怎么不对劲 生病了吗
What do you mean? Like what? Are you sick?
我不知道
I don't know!
- 我感觉很奇怪  - 你生病了吗
- I feel really weird!  - Are you sick?
我觉得我刚感受到了一阵恐慌
I think I'm havin' a panic attack.
什么意思
What do you mean? Hey.
我不知道 我
I don't know, I mean...
你能把那东西拿出去吗 求你了
Could you get that shit outta here, please?
把什么拿出去
Get rid of what?
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know, I don't know!
吃的吗
The food?
你想让我把吃的拿出去
You want me to get rid of the food?
帕特里克
Patrick? Hey.
要带你去医院看看吗
Do you want me to take you to the hospital?
不要 我不知道
No. I don't know.
要给你朋友打电话吗
Do you want me to call your friends?
- 我不知道  - 你想让我怎么做
- I don't know.  - What do you want me to do?
小帕 你要睡了吗
Patty, are you going to bed?
让我静静
Leave me alone.
我觉得我不该让你就这么把门关着
I don't think I should let you keep the door shut.
走开
Just go away.
我会走的 把门打开
I will. Just open up the door.
操
Fuck you.
天哪 你有毛病啊
Jesus Christ, what's your problem?
我说了开门 你是有点崩溃了吗
I said open up the door. Are you havin' a breakdown?
要带你去医院吗
Shall we take you to the hospital?
不要不要不要
No! No! No!
我只是有点抓狂
I'm just freakin' out.
好随你 但我不能让你关着门抓狂
Okay, fine, but I can't let you freak out with the door closed.
如果你每次看到冻鸡肉就要抓狂
And if you're gonna freak out every time
我觉得我们该去医院看看
you see a frozen chicken I think we should go to the hospital.
我对这方面一点都不懂
I don't know anything about this.
我只是不想他呆在冰柜里
I just don't like him bein' in the freezer!
你已经很清楚地表示过了
You've expressed that very clearly.
我也不想
I don't like it either.
我们爱莫能助
There's nothin' we can do about it.
我不烦你 我就坐在这儿
I'm not gonna bother you. I'm just gonna sit here
等你冷静下来
until you calm down.
好了 我现在冷静了
All right, I'm calmer now.
你能走开吗
Can you please just go away?
不能
No.
好棒
Cool!
他们给你多少钱
How much are they payin' you?
最低工资 还有这间房间
Minimum wage plus the room.
好吧
All right.
我们去买点家具
Let's go get some furniture.
我有家具
I got furniture.
你没有
No, you don't.
这不算家具
This doesn't count as furniture.
这不算是个房间
This is not a room.
我们去买点家具
Let's go get some furniture
别烦我了
Get off my back.
小帕过来 我们走
Patty, come on. Let's go.
走吧
Let's go.
好了
There we go.
All right.
好多了吧
Better?
好多了
Better.
听着
So, listen.
我们呆在这里直到你学校放假
We can stay here until your school lets out.
好吗
Okay?
这样我就有时间在波士顿好好安置一下
That'll give me time to set things up in Boston better.
如果你愿意可以在暑假和乔治一起干点活
Maybe you can do some stuff with George in the summer
你的生活也不会一夜间
if you want, and you don't get jerked
翻天覆地
out of your life overnight.
好吗
Okay?
你是询问我的意见还是通知我
Are you askin' me or tellin' me?
- 这是我能做到最好的方式了  - 那你他妈管我愿不愿意
- I'm tellin' you that's the best I can do.  - Then what the fuck do you care whether it's okay with me or not?
才四十五分钟的路
It's 45 minutes away.
- 你想回来随时都可以  - 从昆西回来
- You can come back here any time you want.  - From Quincy?
对啊
Yeah.
要一个多小时 开玩笑吗
It's an hour and a... is that a joke?
至少要一个半小时
It's an hour and a half at least!
- 没开玩笑  - 你要考虑其他车辆因素
- No, it's not.  - You gotta include the other cars!
你坐宇宙飞船也不可能
You couldn't get from here to Roxbury in half an hour
半小时飞到罗克斯伯里
if you flew in a fuckin' spaceship!
好 去你的
Okay, fuck it.
我要午饭钱
I need lunch money.
- 帕特里克  - 帕特里克
- Hey, Patrick!  - Hey, Patrick!
- 帕特里克  - 帕特里克 帕特里克
- Hey, Patrick!  - Patrick! Patrick!
你会去福音吗
So, are you going to godspell?
我还在考虑
I'm thinking about it.
好吧 拜拜
All right, 'Kay. Bye.
那些也是你女朋友
Those your girlfriends, too?
她们倒是想啊
They wish.
你在乔治船上工作他不给你钱吗
Doesn't George give you money for working on his boat?
给的 但我要存下来
Yeah, but I'm savin' that.
- 干吗用  - 买新马达
- For what?  - New motor.
你要去福音
You going to godspell?
拜托
Aw, come on.
Aw, come on!
你好
Hello.
你好 李吗
Hello, Lee?
李
Lee?
李 是你吗
Lee, is that you?
你好
Hello?
你手怎么了
What happened to your hand?
割到了
I cut it.
有那么一瞬间我知道怎么回事
Oh. For a minute there I didn't know what happened.
你有什么理由不告诉我
Is there some reason why you didn't tell me
我妈妈想给我打电话
my mom tried to call me?
她写邮件给我说你把她挂掉了
She wrote me you hung up on her.
她在艾塞克斯
She's in Essex.
她希望我去吃个午饭 见见她未婚夫
She wants me to come have lunch and meet her fiance.
你怎么想的
What'd you think?
她不能联系我
She couldn't get in touch with me?
我挂电话是因为我不知道和她说什么
I hung up on her because I didn't know what to say to her.
我没告诉你是因为
And I didn't tell you because
因为我不知道该怎么和你说
'cause I didn't know what to say to you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你不能阻止我和她联系
You can't stop me talkin' to her.
我才不管你要做什么
I don't give a shit what you do.
你不管 但你却不让我女朋友在这儿过夜
No, but you won't let my girlfriend stay over,
你讨厌我妈以至于她打电话过来都不肯告诉我
you hate my mother so much you won't even tell me she called.
你宁愿把我带去昆西市 毁了我的生活
You'd rather drag me back to Quincy and ruin my life
也不愿让其他人成为我的监护人
than let somebody else be my guardian...
没有什么其他人
There is nobody else.
我可以和我妈住在埃塞克斯
I can live in Essex with my mom.
不 不可以
No, you can't.
她已经不是酒鬼了
She's not an alcoholic anymore
她想让我和她住一起
and she wants me to stay with her,
那样就可以解决我们的问题了
then that solves all our problems.
我仍可以搭同一辆公交去原来的学校
I can take the same bus to my same school
和我所有的朋友在一起
and keep all my friends,
留住小船 你也可以回到波士顿
and the boat, and you can go back to Boston,
还可以回来看看我什么的 如果你想的话
and still check in on me, or whatever, if you want to...
我做不到
I can't do that.
为什么不行
Why not?
小帕 很抱歉我挂了她电话
Patty, I'm sorry I hung up on her.
我会再打给她
I'll call her back,
如果她听上去还像半个人的话
and if she seems semi-human to me,
你可以和她以及她的未婚夫共进午餐
you can go have lunch with her and her fiance.
就这样
That's it.
我不想再多说什么了
I don't wanna talk about this anymore.
好的 一旦到达安全地带
Okay, soon as we're clear,
马上打开它 然后再见机行事
open it up and we'll see what we can do.
好的
Okay.
李
Lee?
最近怎么样
Hey, what do you say?
- 你还好吗  - 我很好 你呢
- How are you?  - Yeah, I'm good. How are you?
还好
All right.
乔的事情 请节哀顺变
I'm really, uh... I'm really sorry to hear about Joe.
心领了 谢谢
I know, yeah, thanks.
帕特里克怎么样
How's Patrick doing?
- 不错  - 是吗
- Good.  - Yeah?
- 是的  - 那就好
- Yeah.  - Good.
怎么了 你来这儿…
What's going on? What are ya...
我回来了
You know, I'm back,
我打算在这儿待到夏天结束
I'm thinking about staying through the summer.
我想看看你这儿有没有什么工作
I was wondering if you had any work.
打发打发时间
I'm looking to pick up some hours.
当然有 有
Sure, sure.
沃尔特去波士顿了 所以…
Walt is down in Boston, so...
- 是吗  - 对 他应该明天回来
- Oh, he is?  - Yeah, he should be back tomorrow
- 你要是想过来  - 他明天回来吗
- if you want to come by.  - He's coming back up tomorrow?
对 给他打个电话
Yeah, yeah. Give him a call.
好 我会给他电话的
Okay. I will give him a call.
- 那样挺好  - 我会打的
- That's a good idea.  - I'll do that.
- 没问题  - 好 好
- Absolutely.  - Okay. All right.
- 很好  - 很高兴见到你
- All right.  - Good to see you.
- 谢了 杰里  - 不客气
- Thanks, Jerry.  - All right.
我不想再在这儿见到他
I don't want to see him in here again.
帕特里克 再见
Bye, Patrick.
周日要去看足球比赛吗
Want to watch the football game on Sunday?
- 好啊  - 帕特里克 再见
- Sure.  - So long, Patrick.
- 帕特里克 再见  - 再见
- Bye, Patrick.  - See you guys.
发动机什么情况
How's the motor?
乔治说活塞随时可能会
George says the piston's gonna go right
卡进缸体
through the block any minute now.
不幸的是 那是个问题
Unfortunately that's a problem.
我们负担不起一艘不能运转的船
We can't afford to keep a boat if we can't run it,
船的发动机坏了的话就运转不了了
and we can't run it if it's got a broken motor.
那我们就去贷款
Let's take out a loan.
然后用什么还呢
And pay it back with what?
我们把它租出去啊 直到挣回贷款的钱
We hire it out 'til we pay the loan back, obviously.
对你来说 不幸的是
Unfortunately for you,
在你满二十一岁之前 你的财产都是归我负责
I'm in charge of your finances until you turn 21,
我不太想替你申请巨额贷款
and I'm not comfortable takin' out enormous loans on your behalf.
我的乐队还要训练
I have band practice.
你能先带我回家拿上东西
Can you drive me home to get my stuff
再送我去桑迪家吗
then drive me over to Sandy's house?
好啊
Sure.
你为什么不去考个驾照 我不是你的专职司机
Why don't you take a drivers'ed course? I'm not your chauffeur.
因为爸爸让我答应他十七岁之前不要开车
'Cause dad made me promise not to drive 'til I was 17.
好吧 那我们还是听你爸的吧
Okay, we'll stick with that then.
你要留下来吃晚饭吗
Do you wanna stay for dinner?
我觉得桑迪的妈妈喜欢你
I think Sandy's mother likes you.
不 哪有
No, she doesn't.
我知道她确实喜欢你
I happen to know that she does.
这可能对我们俩都有好处
This could be good for both of us.
我还是不去了吧
I'd really rather not.
那至少 你能不能和她待半个小时
Well, can you at least just like hang out with her for half an hour
所以我可以在没有桑迪她妈
so I can be alone with Sandy
每二十秒敲一次门的打扰下和她单独相处吗
without her mother knockin' on the door every twenty seconds?
你够了
Come on, man.
你只需要和她说说话
All you gotta do is talk to her.
除了拉着我去见律师
Why can't you help me out a little bit for once
去殡仪馆和太平间
instead of draggin' me to the lawyers
你为什么就不能帮我一次
and the funeral parlor and the morgue?
况且她真的很不错
Anyway, she's really nice.
[响亮乐队]
告诉我为什么
Tell me why
为什么
Why
你为什么需要我
Why do you need me
你为什么想要我
Why do you want me
- 停停停 停  - 你为什么爱我
- Stop, stop, stop, stop. Stop, stop.  - Why do you love me
- 奥托  - 怎么了 我太慢了吗
- Otto...  - What, I'm too slow?
太快了 你拖了
Too fast man. You're dragging.
你太快啦 兄弟
You're way too fast, man.
我太快
I'm too fast.
老兄 你像是比我快一站还不止
Dude, you're like pulling out of the fucking station ahead of me.
天啊 你们 随他去吧
Oh my god, you guys, leave him alone.
老兄 你是认真对待这个乐队吗
Dude, like, are you serious about this band, or what?
好了 行了行了
Okay, all right, all right.
- 饶了他吧  - 少废话
- Just lay off him.  - Get off my back.
好吧 大家都冷静点
All right, everybody just chill here.
我们…我们继续
Let's just, um...let's just go again.
我们是响亮乐队
We are Stentorian.
帕特里克是我最喜欢的人之一
Patrick is one of my favorite people.
那很好
That's good.
你们上面怎么样啊
How's it goin' up there, you guys?
还…还好 谢谢
It's going...it's going fine, thanks!
不过我们正忙着呢
But we're right in the middle of something.
我们正在做繁分数
We're just banging out those compound fractions.
至少我们知道他们在哪里 对吗
At least we know where they are, right?
那倒是
That's true.
你得找多少个才能
How many of those you generally gotta go through
选出一个你喜欢的
before you pick a winner?
我倒想看看你在各种打扰的情况下
I'd like to see you use one of these goddamn things
用一次这个鬼东西
with all these interruptions.
我操
Oh, fuck me!
怎么了 你还好吗
What happened? Are you ok?
我被你的玩偶之家绊倒了
I tripped over your fuckin' doll house.
天啊 你有没有把它摔坏
Oh my god, did you break it?
我不知道 不过我没事
I don't know. I'm fine though, by the way.
我的天
Oh my god.
那是我五岁的时候我外婆给我的
My grandmother gave me that when I was five years old.
那还是她小时候玩的玩偶之家
It was literally her doll house from when she was a little girl.
那为什么把它放在地上
Then what's it doin' on the fuckin' floor?
玩偶之家不在地上玩在哪玩
It's a doll house, that's where you play with it!
孩子们 上面怎么了
Kids, what is going on up there?
没啥 帕特里克脚趾踢到了外婆的玩偶之家
Nothing! Patrick just stubbed his toe on mummer's doll house,
不过没什么事
but it's okay!
桑迪 那是我妈的娃娃屋
Sandy, that doll house belonged to my mother.
- 我知道 妈妈  - 如果你把它摔碎了
- Yes I know, mom.  - If you're gonna smash it to pieces...
没人要把它摔成碎片 它没事
Nobody is smashin' it to pieces! It's fine!
吉尔 别担心 我没事
Don't worry, Jill, I'm okay.
我的脚趾也会好的
My toe's gonna be okay.
你到底想不想上我
Do you want to fuck me or not?
想
Yes.
要再给你拿杯啤酒吗 李
Could I get you another beer, Lee?
不用了 谢谢
I'm good. Thank you.
能失陪一下吗 李 一会儿
Would you excuse me, Lee, one sec?
好
Sure.
- 戴上了吗  - 是啊 简直是奇迹
- Is it on?  - Yes. It's a miracle.
好 快点
Okay, hurry up.
等一下
One second please!
赶紧滚开
Get outta my way!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
什么事
What's up?
真的很抱歉 我知道你们在努力学习
I'm really sorry, I know you're trying to work,
但是我实在是在楼下待不住了
but I can't sit down there much longer.
为什么 什么问题
Why? What's the problem?
他不愿意说话
He won't talk.
半个小时内我一直在试图和他聊天
I've been trying to make conversation for half an hour.
- 我知道我不是世上  - 你说真的吗
- I realize I'm not ...  - Are you serious?
怎么了
What's the matter?
- 最迷人的人  - 妈
- the most fascinating person in the world...  - Mom!
但真的太令人不安了
But it's very, very strained.
- 什么事  - 她无法让你叔叔开口聊天
- What's going on?  - She can't get your uncle to talk.
他喜欢体育
He likes sports.
很抱歉扫你们兴了
I'm sorry to bust things up,
但是你们大概还要多久
but how much longer do you think you're gonna be?
或许你可以打开电视比赛
Could you maybe turn on a game?
- 抱歉  - 闭嘴
- I'm sorry.  - Shut up.
妈妈 求你了
Mummy, please.
你真是帮了大忙了
You were a tremendous help.
我可没要求去那坐一坐
I didn't ask to sit down there.
你就不能像其他成人一样聊个天吗
You can't make small talk like every other grown up in the world?
- 不行  - 你就不能瞎扯半个小时吗
- No.  - You can't talk about boring bullshit for half an hour?
- 不行  - 谈谈那些利率怎么样
- No.  - Hey, how about those interest rates?
[AAA卡为一种打折卡]
- 不 不行  - 我把我的AAA卡弄丢了
- No, I can't.  - Hey, I lost my triple A card.
- 不行  - 像其他人一样
- Nope.  - Like everybody else?
不行 抱歉
Nope, sorry.
你他妈真是个混蛋
You're a fucking asshole.
你说她住在哪来着
Where'd you say she lives?
这儿房子也没有 什么都没有
'Cause there's, like, no houses here. None.
什么情况 她住在睡袋里吗
What, does she live in a fucking sleeping bag?
鸽山街一百一十九号
119 pigeon hill street.
鸽山街还是鸽山路
Pigeon hill street, or pigeon hill road?
- 鸽山街  - 好的 鸽山街
- Pigeon hill street  - Okay, pigeon hill street.
- 鸽山苑  - 街
- Pigeon hill court.  - Street.
- 鸽山路  - 街
- Pigeon hill road.  - Street.
- 行 鸽山…  - 鸽山街
- Fine, pigeon hill...  - Pigeon hill street.
- 这是鸽山路  - 好吧
- This is pigeon hill road.  - Okay.
你没有GPS定位吗
You have no GPS whatsoever?
没 我只有卡通片
No, I have a little fucking cartoon.
- 你想让我帮你输进去吗  - 不 不用
- You want me to punch it in for you?  - No, I don't.
我搞好了 谢谢
I've got it, thank you.
行了 听着
Okay, listen.
你紧张吗
Are you nervous?
是啊 我紧张
Yeah, I'm nervous.
你是什么 他妈的天才吗
What are you, a fuckin' genius?
好吧 不说了
Okay, skip it.
如果觉得怪怪的 就发短信给我
Just want you to text me if anything gets weird.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
天啊 是我的帕特里克吗
Oh my gosh. Is that my Patrick?
妈妈
Hi, mom.
我太开心了
I'm so happy.
进来吧 欢迎来我家
Come in. Welcome to my home.
帕特里克 这是我丈夫
Patrick. This is my fella.
杰弗里 这是帕特里克
Jeffrey, this is Patrick...
很高兴终于见到你了 帕特里克
Great to finally meet you, Patrick.
- 很高兴认识你  - 是啊
- Nice to meet you.  - Yeah.
这位是李
And this is Lee.
欢迎
Hey, welcome.
- 谢谢  - 我是杰弗里
- Thanks.  - Jeffrey.
我是李
Lee.
李 你真的不留下来吃午饭吗
Now, Lee, are you sure you can't stay for lunch?
不了
I'm positive. Yeah.
好了
All right.
来 快来
Come, come.
真的不用我帮忙吗
Oh, are you sure... I can't help you...
不用了 谢谢亲爱的
No thanks, honey.
你放轻松就行了
Your job is to relax.
这是你的首要任务 知道了吗
That is your number one assignment, okay?
好吧 那我就专心吃
Okay, all right. I'm really gonna apply myself.
我刚刚只是在开玩笑
No, I was just joking.
我知道 我也是
I know you were. So was I.
你们俩处得怎么样
How we gettin' along?
- 很好  - 很好
- Great.  - Great.
你不用那么客气的
You don't have to be so polite, you know.
我没有客气
I'm not being polite.
你想不想吃饭前先洗个手
Did you wanna wash your hands before we eat?
好
Yes.
感谢主赐予我们美食
For what we are about to receive, let us give thanks.
- 阿门  - 阿门
- Amen.  - Amen.
你可以说“阿门” 帕特里克
You can say "Amen", Patrick.
没人要招募你入教会
Nobody's tryin' to recruit you.
我说了“阿门”
I did say "Amen".
说了吗 好吧
Oh, you did? Okay.
你不是非得要说的
Well, you don't have to.
我知道 我只是说得很小声
Yeah, I know. I just said it really quietly.
没关系 亲爱的
It's fine, honey.
我知道我会让你感到惊讶
Look, I know I'm gonna be a shock to you.
很多方面都会
In a lot of ways.
希望是好的惊喜
I'm hoping it's a good shock.
是的
Yeah.
你还需要什么吗 帕特里克
You need anything else, Patrick?
我希望食物都合你口味
I hope everything's okay.
是的 食物都很好吃
Oh yeah, everything's great.
你跟我说话不需要这么正式
You don't have to be so formal.
我没有
I'm not.
你妈妈是希望你…
I think your mother wants you to feel...
我想说的是 这里也是你的家
I'm just sayin' that this is your home, too.
希望你把这当成家
I want it to be.
我知道…
And I know...
I know, uh...
你的生活发生了许多改变
Things are different for you.
算了 我也说不好
Anyway, I don't know.
没关系
That's okay.
你在学校学些什么呢 帕特里克
What are you studying at school, Patrick?
都是平常的东西
Oh, well, the usual stuff.
我去去就回来
You know what? I'm gonna be right back.
你们需要我从厨房拿点什么吗
Does anybody need anything from the kitchen?
- 不用 谢谢 谢谢  - 不用了
- No, thanks. Thank you.  - I'm good, no.
豆角你尝过了吗
Did you get some string beans?
还没 谢谢
Oh, no, not yet. Thank you.
我去…
Let me, um...
我去看看她在里头干吗
Let me just see what she's doin' in there.
她是什么样的人
So what was she like?
说不好 她挺紧张的
I don't know. She was pretty nervous.
是吗
Yeah?
那个男人呢
What was that guy like?
很虔诚的基督教徒
He was very Christian.
你知道我们也是基督教徒吧
You know, we're Christian, too, right?
我知道
Yes, I know that.
你知道天主教也属于基督教吧
You are aware that catholics are christians?
我知道
Yes, I am aware of that.
反正她听起来比以前好多了
Well, it sounds like she's doing better, anyway.
她没酗酒了
She's not drinking.
也没在精神病院
She's not in the psych ward.
怎么了
Wow, what?
你为了甩掉我 真是什么都做得出来
You'll do anything to get rid of me.
- 什么  - 你听到了
- What?  - You heard me.
不是那样的
That's not true.
亲爱的帕特里克
Dear Patrick,
我写信是要感谢你今天的拜访
I'm writing to thank you for today.
你的到来对你妈妈意义重大
Your visit meant the world to your mom.
你愿意重新进入她的生活 代表了你对她的爱和信任
We are both deeply grateful for the love and trust
为此我们两个都十分感恩
you've shown by offering to rejoin her life,
然而催促她踏上这段漫长而充满挑战的路途
but I feel it would be unfair to your mom to rush her along
对你妈妈来说很不公平
the long and challenging road ahead,
所以以后请你写信给我
and so I'm going to ask you to write to me
来安排进一步的见面
in future to arrange any further visits.
希望你不要觉得我在干涉你
I hope you won't take this as an intrusion...
你的朋友们今晚在哪
where are your friends tonight?
不知道
I don't know.
不如你打电话给叫桑迪那个女孩
Why don't you call that girl Sandy,
- 看她要不要过来  - 不用了 谢谢
- see if she'll come over?  - No, thanks.
不过想法不错
Nice try, though.
你要朝谁开枪 你还是我
Who are you going to shoot, you or me?
你知道这些值多少钱吗
Do you know what these things are worth?
不知道
No.
我想把它们卖掉
Want to try and sell them
这样就能给你的船买个发动机了
so you can have a motor for the boat?
这真是个好主意
That's a really good idea.
太棒了
This is awesome.
你想开吗
Do you want to drive?
当然了
Sure.
好的
All right.
天啊
Oh! Oh, my god!
- 真抱歉  - 没关系
- I'm so sorry.  - That's all right.
没关系 把船开直就好
That's all right. That's all right. Just straighten her out.
- 天啊  - 把她开直
- Oh, my god.  - Straighten her out.
- 没事的  - 对不起
- That's okay.  - Sorry.
我得去处理一些杂事
Hey, I got to run some chores.
几小时后就回来
I'll be back in a couple hours.
- 想要我带点什么吗  - 不用 谢了
- You want anything?  - No, thank you.
不用了 谢谢 钱德勒先生
No, thanks, Mr. Chandler.
谢谢
Thank you.
多好的城市
Set-up city.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
不是吗 那塞尔维·麦甘恩呢
Oh, yeah? How Sylvie McGann?
谁
Who?
快开门吧
Just open the door.
我不认为这是我们的责任 不过…
I didn't think it was our responsibility, but...
对啊 他们本可以…
Yeah, I guess. I mean, they could have...
没事的
it's okay.
李
Lee.
你好
Hi.
瑞秋 这是李
Rachel, this is Lee.
- 你好  - 李 这是瑞秋
- Hello.  - Lee, this is Rachel.
还有 这是迪伦
And this is Dylan.
你看不清他的脸
You can't see him too good.
你好 迪伦
Hi, Dylan.
很帅啊
Very handsome.
兰迪 我去开车过来接你吧
Randi, you want me to get the car and pick you up?
- 好  - 没事 我要走了
- Yeah.  - That's okay. I got to go.
其实我们能不能
Actually, could... could we, uh,
能不能聊一会
could we talk for a second?
- 当然  - 好的
- Sure.  - Okay.
我停在路边等你 几分钟就到
I'll just pull around. Just be a few minutes.
- 好的 谢谢  - 很高兴认识你
- Okay. Thanks.  - Nice to meet you.
- 我也是  - 我马上回来
- Yeah. You, too.  - Be right back.
我没什么重要的事要说
I don't have anything big to say.
没关系
That's okay.
我只是…
I just...
我知道你回来了 我…
I know you've been around, and I...
我一直忙着安顿帕特里克
I've just been getting Patrick settled in.
他好像适应得还不错
It seems like he's doing pretty good, huh?
总的来说
Considering.
我觉得挺不错了
I think he is, yeah.
你可能不知道
I guess you don't know this,
但我…
but I, uh...
我一直跟乔伊保持着联系
I really kept in touch with Joe.
- 我知道  - 这阵子见不到帕特里克
- No, I knew that.  - It's been kind of weird
我觉得有点怪怪的 好吧
for me not seeing Patrick. Oh. Oh, okay.
我以为你不知道
I... I didn't know.
你想见他就去见吧
Uh, you could see him if you want.
我们还能一起吃午餐吗
Could we ever have lunch?
你是指你和我吗
You mean us, you and me?
是的
Yeah.
因为我…
Because I, uh...
我以前对你说了很多过分的话
I said a lot of terrible things to you.
没有
No.
可是我…
But I...
我知道你从来没有…
I know you never...
可能你不想跟我说话了
maybe you don't want to talk to me.
- 不是这样的  - 让我说完
- It's not that.  - Let me finish.
无论…
However...
我的心已经支离破碎
my heart was broken.
永远都无法愈合
It's always going to be broken.
我知道你的心也碎了
And I know yours is broken, too.
但我不用背负…
But I don't have to carry...
我说过的话…
I said things that...
我对你说过那些话 我真该下地狱
I should fucking burn in hell for what I said to you.
不是的
No. No.
- 真的…  - 不 不
- It was...  - no, no, no, no.
兰迪 别
Randi, no.
我真的很抱歉
I'm just sorry.
这… 我…我无法解… 无法…
It... I... I can't ex... I can't...
我爱你
I love you.
我可能不应该那么说
Maybe I shouldn't say that.
不 你可以说
No, you can say that.
只是…
It's just...
抱歉 我该走了
I'm sorry. I've got to go.
我们不能一起吃午餐吗
We couldn't have lunch?
真的很抱歉 还是不要了
I'm really sorry. I don't think so.
你刚才说的那些就足够了
I thank you for saying everything you said.
你不能就这样消沉下去
You can't just die.
我没有 我没有 我没有
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not.
但亲爱的 亲爱的
But, honey... honey...
我 我想让你快乐
And I... I want you to be happy.
亲爱的 当我在这遇到了你
Honey, I see you walking around here,
我就是想告诉你
and I just want to tell you...
我想告诉你 兰迪
I would want to talk to you, Randi,
- 但是 李  - 我 我 我
- But, Lee...  - Please, I... I... I...
因为我
because... I...
- 李  - 我
- Lee...  - Um, I'm...
- 我想  - 李 你
- I'm trying to...  - Lee, you've got to...
我不知道
I don't know what...
这并不是
Look, this is not...
我并不想折磨你
I don't want to torture you.
你没有折磨我
You're not torturing me.
我就是想告诉你
I just want to tell you
我错了
that I was wrong.
你没错 没有
No. No.
你不了解我 这其实
You don't understand. There's nothing...
这其实没什么大不了的
there's nothing there.
- 没什么大不了的  - 你骗我
- There's nothing there.  - That's not true.
- 你骗我  - 就是这样
- That's not true.  - Let me say this.
你不了解我
You don't understand.
- 我了解你  - 我不知道该
- I understand you.  - I don't know what to...
我知道你了解我
I know you understand me.
我 我 我得走了
I... I... I've got to go.
- 不要  - 对不起
- Don't.  - I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
角落球袋
Corner pocket.
- 抱歉  - 没事
- Pardon me.  - It's all right.
他妈的
Shit.
看见没
Did you see that?
想跟我们打吗
You want to hit us? Want to hit us?
- 他妈的  - 你个狗杂种
- God damn it!  - Come on, you little bastard!
小心 小心 小心
Look out, look out, look out.
Look out, look out, look out!
快停下 别打了
Get off him! Break it up!
住手 乔治
Back off, George!
- 他妈的  - 乔治 快出去
- Fuck him!  - George, get out of here!
- 让他住手  - 乔治
- Break him up!  - George!
让他出去 乔治
Get him out of here, George!
他是乔伊·钱德勒的弟弟
He's Joey Chandler's brother.
- 别打了 别打了  - 他妈的
- Back off, back off.  - Fucking dude...
- 他妈的  - 冷静
- Oh, fuck...  - Hey, settle down.
操 操
Fuck him! Fuck him!
- 他就是个傻逼  - 冷静
- He's a fucking douche bag!  - Settle down.
冷静 算你们赢了 好吧
Settle down. You won, all right?
狗娘养的
Fuck that motherfucker.
- 冷静  - 好了
- Settle down.  - Okay, brother.
- 消气了吧  - 你们赢了 好吧
- You good?  - You won, all right?
- 没事了  - 操
- Are we cool?  - Fuck him.
去他妈的
Fuck him!
别打了 别打了
Come here. Get off.
- 别打了 别打了  - 快停下
- Get off. Get off.  - Leave him...
- 操  - 别他妈打了
- Fuck you!  - Get the fuck off. Get him...
该送他去医院吗
Should he go to the hospital?
不用吧 没骨折
I don't think so. Nothing's broken.
这群混蛋用什么打的他
What did they fucking hit him with,
棒球棒吗
a baseball bat?
他们都说是他起的头
They all just said he started swinging.
帕特里克呢
Where's Patrick?
他和孩子们在一起
He's with the kids.
我让他们出去买汉堡
I sent them out for burgers.
不行 不行
No, no, no, no.
- 李 快坐下  - 坐下
- Lee, sit down.  - Sit down.
坐下 没事的
Sit down. It's all right.
- 我应该给你们点钱 李  - 没事的 不用
- Let me give you some money.  - Lee, please, I got it.
- 我把钱给你  - 快收起来
- I'll give you some money.  - Put that away.
- 我说了不用  - 把钱收起来
- Please, no. I got it.  - Put your money away.
- 拿着  - 不用了
- Come on.  - I got it.
不用了 我付就行了
I got it. It's on me.
我给你煮了咖啡 喝了吧
I made you some coffee. Come on. Drink this.
- 喝吧  - 喝吧
- Come on.  - Come on.
喝吧
Come on, buddy.
起码喝一点
Just have a little.
没事了
It's all right.
我拿点冰块给你敷脸
I'm going to get you some ice for your face, okay?
没事了
It's all right.
用我帮你拿点什么吗 李叔叔
Can I get you anything, uncle Lee?
不用了 谢谢你
Oh, no, thanks, buddy.
好吧 那我去睡了
All right. I'm going to go to bed.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Good night.  - Good night.
托马斯
Thomas.
冲向篮筐 得两分
Drives to the basket, gets two.
正如大家所料
That's what you want.
爸爸
Daddy.
怎么了 宝贝
Yes, honey?
你看不见我们身上着火了吗
Can't you see we're burning?
不 宝贝 你们身上没着火
No, honey. You're not burning.
起火了 起火了
Fire. Fire.
李叔叔 什 什么味啊
Uncle Lee, what... what is that smell?
我把调味汁弄糊了 没事
I just burned the sauce. Everything's okay.
对了
Yeah.
我在波士顿找到了工作 七月份开始
I got a job in Boston. Starts in July.
什么工作
What is it?
看门人 杂务工
Custodian, handyman.
但这次只是负责两栋楼 所以
But it's just two buildings this time, so...
那我们这次又住在波士顿
And what, uh, delightful Boston neighborhood
哪个环境宜人的地方呢
have you selected for us to live in?
- 哪也不住  - 什么意思
- None.  - What do you mean?
你不用搬去波士顿
You don't have to move to Boston.
我要去查尔斯镇
I want to be in Charlestown,
以后由乔治照顾你
and George is going to take you.
什么
What?
我上周和他谈过了
I talked to him last week
跟他解释过了目前的情况
and explained the situation to him.
小乔吉秋季要去波士顿大学
Georgie Junior's going to BU in the fall,
吉米明年毕业
and Jimmy graduates next year.
在你十八岁之前 房子可以出租
We can rent this house out until you turn 18.
你愿意的话可以回来住
Then you come back and stay if you want.
当你到二十一岁了就可以把房子卖了
When you turn 21, you're allowed to sell it
或者留着还是其它别的
or keep it or whatever you want to do.
夏天一过必须把船租出去
We definitely have to hire out the boat when summer's over.
我们之前谈过的
Just like we talked about.
等你拿到了执照
When you get your license,
要是真拿到了
then we can... we can just figure that out
再做讨论也不迟
when it happens.
我还是受托人
I'm still the trustee.
但所有乔给我留下的财产
But all the financial stuff that Joe set up for me
都将转移到乔治的名下
is going to get transferred over to George.
所以基本一切照旧
So basically everything's staying the same,
除了你不用搬家了
except you don't have to move.
谢谢 但 谁
Thank you, but, like, who's...
是他们当我的监护人还是你
Are they going to be my guardians, or are you going...
他们打算收养你
They're going to adopt you.
总之 这是我的计划
Anyway, that's just how I set it up.
你不必勉强 由你决定
You don't have to. It's up to you.
所以你就这么一走了之吗
So you're just going to disappear?
不是
No.
当然不是
我这么计划是想让你待在这
I set it up this way so you could stay here.
他们很高兴能收养你
And they're really glad to have you.
- 他们  - 我知道 我知道
- They...  - I know, I know.
他们是很好 但
I mean, they're great, but...
你为什么不能留下
Why can't you stay?
小帕
Come on, Patty.
我受不了了
I can't beat it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
情况怎么样
What do you think?
没什么大问题
It's going to be okay.
你是斯坦 钱德勒的儿子吗
Are you one of Stan Chandler's boys?
恩 我是李
Yeah. I'm Lee.
很久以前 我和你父亲下过棋
I used to play chess with your father a long time ago.
他棋下得很好
He was a excellent chess player.
没错
That's him.
他已经过世了 是吧
He's not still living, is he?
恩
No.
我听说他的一个儿子
One of the sons
最近去世了
passed away recently, I heard.
恩 是我的哥哥乔
Uh, yeah, my brother Joe.
他是个很好的人
Very personable man.
没错
Yeah.
我父亲一九五九年去世的
My father passed away in 1959.
英年早逝
A young man.
他在一艘捕金枪鱼船上工作
He worked on a tuna boat.
一个很平常的日子
He got up one morning.
不是什么极端天气
Some weather, nothing dramatic.
他却再也没有回来
And he never returned.
没有信号 也没有求救
No signals, no maydays.
谁也不知道他发生了什么
No one ever found out what happened to him.
[出租]
钱德勒家族
斯坦利·A
克劳蒂娅·玛丽
约瑟夫·R
我去买点冰淇凌
I'm going to get some ice cream.
去吧
Go ahead.
能给我点钱吗
Can I have some money?
当然
Yes.
我什么时候搬到乔吉家
So when am I supposed to move in with Georgie?
七月
July.
我现在都没有住的地方
I don't even have a place to live yet.
他们不给你提供住宿吗
They don't give you an apartment?
提供了 但我想找一个有两间房的
Yeah, but I'm looking for one with an extra room.
一间放个可以当床用的沙发或是
A room for a pull-out sofa or...
要那个干吗
What for?
等你来时候用呗
So you can come visit some time.
或者你想读波士顿的大学
Or if you want to look at colleges in Boston,
可以在那过夜
you could stay overnight.
我不打算读大学
I'm not going to college.
好吧 那就改放我的那些废物吧
All right, then I'll have an extra room for all my shit.
非得现在说这个吗
Do we have to talk about this now?
不
No.
扔得好
Great throw.
别管它了
Just let it go.
当心
Heads up.